<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Anarchy.zip</path>
		<name>Anarchy</name>
		<desc>As a Defender clone, Anarchy is a sidescrolling parallax shooter, in which you take on the evil Anarchists and their destructive behaviour. Your ship moves left or right on a looping level, shooting the enemies and finally the bosses. You have a single life with gradually draining energy. No less than 50 High Scores are recorded.

There are no surprises in gameplay, except the usual upgrades for your ship - X-shaped pods reveal circles, which can be collected to produce multiple fire beams, multi-directional shots, and drones with advanced cannons

The action is fast and smooth, and anybody looking for a straight shooter might take a glimpse, although the reviews from the magazines mostly ranged from bad to mid-class.

Anarchy was released under Psygnosis label Psyclapse. The manual comes in four languages: English, French, German and Italian.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<developer>Psyclapse</developer>
		<publisher>WJS Design</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Baseball.zip</path>
		<name>Championship Baseball</name>
		<desc>In this traditional baseball simulation, gameplay takes place mainly on a split screen.One side shows an overview of the field, the other showing the batter, with the latter view disappearing when the ball is hit.

The game requires you to "draft" a team before play, composing the best possible squad based on each player's skill attributes. The game also allows a semblance of managerial control, and has an optional batting practice mode to warm up. It then allows you to play individual games, or participate in a 4 division, 24-team championship.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gamestar</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elemental.zip</path>
		<name>Elemental</name>
		<desc>Elemental is set on the planet of the same name. The player takes the role of a two-year old Roundline, basically a living ball, who has to pass the great ordeal.

Every of the 32 levels plays out on a non-scrolling field where the player has to evade two enemies and touch certain tiles. This causes objects to appear which can be picked up and dropped at another place. If an enemy touches an object, it transforms into a pill which also has to be picked up and dropped elsewhere. There are save tiles where the enemies can't touch the player.</desc>
		<publisher>Lankhor</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./No Excuses.zip</path>
		<name>No Excuses</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Arcana</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blood Money.zip</path>
		<name>Blood Money</name>
		<desc>The speech in the introductory sequence probably sums things up best - "the biggest unanswered question is 'where is the money?"

The player has 4 missions to take on, in each case trying to kill baddies for the money they have, which can be spent in the shop rooms to upgrade their craft. Energy is depleted by contact with enemies and the walls, although there are some baddies who simply hover on your ship and steal, rather than physically doing damage.

The game is a shoot 'em up which scrolls both horizontally and vertically, while being viewed from an R-Type style sideways perspective. Navigating the levels sometimes requires the player to duck through gaps in scenery.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pawn, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Pawn</name>
		<desc>The aim of this interactive fiction with graphics is to escape from the land of Kerovnia, where strange occurrences are routine. The Roobikyoub dwarves have been banished from the kingdom, which is not good as they produce high-quality whisky. King Erik is not popular for this decision, as some feel that ale brewers and mineral water bottlers have influenced him. Honest John the trader and Kronos the Magician play a key role in your journey, each offering sub-quests to attempt.

The package includes a novella complete with map and decipherable hints, which are accessed by typing 'hint' followed by the code into the computer. Therefore, those with only a pirated copy would struggle to complete the game.

Your score and the number of locations visited are both displayed in the title bar. The parser allows whole words to be deleted and unaccepted previous entries to be re-edited.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magnetic Scrolls</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Manhattan Dealers.zip</path>
		<name>Manhattan Dealers</name>
		<desc>You're Dirty Harry and you need to find and beat up dealers to get drugs and burn them outside the town, which will regain your energy. This is the Silmarils' first game. In 9 screens, you can fight with ninjas, amazons, punks and other thugs and low-lives, and you've only your hands and feets for that !</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silmarils</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Briga de rua</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warlock.zip</path>
		<name>Warlock - The Avenger</name>
		<desc>A follow-up to the mid-80s Gauntlet clone Druid, which saw the series move up onto 16-bit systems.nnThe gameplay involves guiding your character through a succession of 8 mazes. The standard bad guys are there, as are items to pick up including health and extra weapons.nnThe game gives you one life, whcih represents the gradually declining amount of energy. You should get further on each go, with the difficulty curve being quite precise.nnAs a bonus, an exclusive conversion of Druid is included.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electralyte</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battlehawks 1942.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Hawks 1942</name>
		<desc>Fly as an American or Japanese pilot in one of 4 operations in the Pacific Theatre during WWII. This simulation can also qualify as educational software because the manual features tons of historical information. Twelve aircraft (including variants) and about 20 types of ships are represented. First of the Lucasfilm/Lawrence Holland WWII air combat trilogy.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lucasfilm Games</developer>
		<publisher>Lucasfilm Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dick Tracy.zip</path>
		<name>Dick Tracy</name>
		<desc>Dick Tracy is a tie in to the 1990 movie adaptation of the classic comic strip, staring Warren Beatty and Madonna.
While an action/adventure hybrid using this license was released by Disney for the PC and Amiga, Titus also held a license to the movie.  This is a side scrolling action game, where you control Dick Tracy as he moves through five stages, shooting gangsters with an assortment of weapons.  Each stage leads to one of the mob bosses, until you ultimately capture the big man himself.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Logical.zip</path>
		<name>Log!cal</name>
		<desc>Logical is a bizarre puzzle game in which you have to arrange colored balls (green, purple, blue or yellow) to form quartets in any of several locations on the game board. These locations are, in fact, balls you can spin, then send any of the balls in them through the connection path (have a look at the screenshots).</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Operation Thunderbolt.zip</path>
		<name>Operation Thunderbolt</name>
		<desc>Operation Thunderbolt is the exciting sequel to Operation Wolf. An airliner is hijacked by terrorists en-route from Paris to Boston, who threaten to kill all hostages on board if their mates aren't released from jail. Instead of reaching its destination, the airliner makes a landing in Kalubya, Africa, and all the hostages are hidden in various locations. The authorities have asked the hero from Operation Wolf to rescue the hostages, but only this time, the hero brings his friend along for the ride.

There are eight missions to complete in Operation Thunderbolt, and each one has you shooting down soldiers, choppers, and tanks. The gameplay varies every one or two missions. In some missions, you are driving a jeep or controlling a boat, while in others, you are walking while you're shooting. You have a limited supply of ammo, and a limited supply of rocket bombs, but you can always stock up by shooting down crates falling from the sky, or by killing a cat or dog that get in the line of fire. Also from crates, you can get special items like bulletproof vests, rocket bombs, and different weapons.

You also have a life bar to worry about. If you're shot at by soldiers, or if rocket bombs or grenades are thrown at you, you 'll lose energy, and once you're energy is depleted,  you lose one of your three lives. You can lose a lot of energy by killing hostages on purpose,  and you can't easily avoid killing them if you decide to use rocket bombs to wipe out enemies. The eighth mission, the mission that involves you fighting terrorists on a plane,  proves to be difficult because a woman in a blue dress stands up and gets in the line of fire, and you have to very careful when you're going to use rocket bombs.

There are two endings to this game, and which ending you can watch will depend on the number of hostages you've saved, and whether or not you shot the pilot instead of the mission eight boss.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Tiro com acessórios</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomb Jack.zip</path>
		<name>Bombjack</name>
		<desc>In Bomb Jack, the player controls Jack, who must collect all the bombs in order to complete the current round and go onto the next one. This sounds easy, right? Wrong! Making Jack's task difficult are numerous enemies such as birds, mummies, turtles, and orbs.

In each round, collecting a number of bombs results in a bonus coin appearing, and collecting this coin will make the player's score increase 2 to 4 times. More often than not, the "power ball" appears, and when you collect this, you can defeat enemies and have more time to collect all the bombs. There is also the "E" coin, which gives Jack one additional life, but rarely does this coin appear.

The more you progress through the game, the more difficult it becomes, as enemies travel more quickly to get you.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradox Development</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Football Manager 2.zip</path>
		<name>Football Manager 2</name>
		<desc>Football Manager from Addictive was the first game of its kind, and this sequel followed several years later, absorbing ideas from the many similar games released in between. Teams can now choose formations, and assign man-to-man marking. Players have individual skills and fitness ratings, in a more realistic way, with half-time substitutions and tactical changes supported. The whole 92-club league is incorporated, as is the League Cup alongside the FA Cup. It is now possible to watch and assess the individual performance of the players, with match graphics differentiating the attack / midfield / defense areas more clearly. Training allows passing length and height to be specified.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Addictive Games</developer>
		<publisher>Addictive Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghosts'n Goblins.zip</path>
		<name>Ghosts 'n' Goblins</name>
		<desc>Ghosts'n Goblins is a sideways scrolling action platformer spread over six levels, each of which must be completed within three minutes (or a life is lost), taking in forest, mountain and cavern settings.Arthur the brave knight must rescue his lady from t</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Immortal.zip</path>
		<name>The Immortal</name>
		<desc>The Immortal is an isometric action-adventure game.

Your old mentor Mordamir has disappeared. Probably kidnapped. You're not too sure where he might be, but a dungeon is always a good place to look, so you seek out the nearest one and plunge into its depths. Beware: 8 levels of 
isometric death await.

The Immortal is the prototype of a trial-and-error game. Progress is made by encountering a hazard, dying, solving the problem, encountering the next hazard. To solve a level, you have to know its traps and their patterns by heart. As frustrating as this may sound (it is), The Immortal quite cleverly balances annoyance with curiosity and graphical rewards. In short: You want to see what challenge lies in the next room.

The puzzles range from simple avoidance of traps to the correct use of items; you collect objects in an inventory. Every now and then, The Immortal surprises with a special challenge. For example, you've got to ride a magic carpet through a hallway full of fire traps, or ride a barrel on an underground river. The dungeon isn't empty: some friedlies may have valuable information or trade items, the nasty sort of guys will attack. Combat is fought man-to-man on a special screen. Your adversary indicates his next attack a few seconds before he executes it, so you've got time to react appropriately. You can dodge to the left or the right, as well as attack from these two directions. There is no save option in the game, of course, but you may restart each level as often as you like. Levels can be skipped by entering passwords.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sandcastle</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynasty Wars.zip</path>
		<name>Dynasty Wars</name>
		<desc>Conversion of the Capcom arcade to home computers. The player adopts the identity of an ancient Chinese warrior, and riding on horseback has to eliminate all his opponents, mostly infantry and archers.

The game uses a lateral scroll and the player can move in all four directions. A novelty is the attack system: when pressing fire the energy of the attack will load up as the warrior moves his spear up and backwards, in order to gain momentum. The more the player can keep fire pressed, the more powerful the attack will be.

The game spawned a sequel in the arcades, "Warriors of fate", and is not to be confused with the PSX game of the same title, which is a one-on-one fighting game.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Ninja 3.zip</path>
		<name>Last Ninja 3</name>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blasteroids.zip</path>
		<name>Blasteroids</name>
		<desc>Como o nome sugere, esta conversão arcade atualiza a jogabilidade básica do Asteroids. Isso significa dizer que a jogabilidade principal consiste em voar através de níveis de tela única, atirando em rochas, que se dividem em rochas menores quando atingidas, tornando-se pequenas o suficiente para desaparecer.

Neste caso, os Asteróides estão protegendo Mukor, um ser maligno que está envenenando planetas sob o controle da Corporação Colonizadora.
Cada nível é dividido em 9 ou 16 sub-níveis, que são escolhidos através de um quadrado no qual qualquer nível restante adjacente ao último nível concluído pode ser selecionado. Existem 3 naves diferentes (Speeder, Fighter e Warrior), que podem ser alternadas entre a qualquer momento. Power-ups (incluindo armas melhoradas, recargas de escudo e um impulso mais rápido) podem ser coletados voando para eles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imageworks</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Rabbits.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Rabbits</name>
		<desc>The rabbit you control has ninja skills and an appropriate costume. Ninja Rabbits is a platform game where you usually go to the right, except sometimes you must go down into the sewers or metro and fight there. Enemies on various levels include street thugs, ninjas, bears and frogs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flair Software</developer>
		<publisher>Micro Value</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Official Everton F.C. Intelligensia, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Official Everton F.c. Intelligensia</name>
		<desc>The Official Everton F.C. Intelligensia is a quiz game about football. Despite the title it's not specifically about Everton as the player can choose to represent any English top flight team of the 1989/90 season and it features question about both domestic and international football. All questions have three alternatives to choose from and has to be done before time runs out. Some are accompanied with a picture.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Official Everton F.C. Intelligensia, The-image.png</image>
		<publisher>Amfas Computer Software Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Quiz / Inglês</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hammerfist.zip</path>
		<name>Hammerfist</name>
		<desc>In a grim future, the people are kept under control by a horde of genetically-modified beings who look identical to everyone else, and appear to act the same, but are subtly controlling minds and actions. This works perfectly for Centro-Holographis until two of their droids, Hammerfist (male) and Metalisis (female) malfunction. They try to put things right, and come under your control in this side-view action game with adventure elements.

You can switch between the two characters at any moment, and must use this wisely as their abilities differ greatly. On each screen you must kill all enemies, as well as taking out the robots which keep the doors locked.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vivid Image</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twylyte.zip</path>
		<name>Twylyte</name>
		<desc>Twylyte is an arcade 3D shoot-em-up in the tradition of Space Harrier and Backlash. The player drives towards the horizon continuously at enormous speed. There are indestructible barriers which the invisible player ship must avoid contact with, as well as enemies shooting and firing missiles at the player. Beside moving left and right, the ship can also moved up and down, which adds further possibilities to evade the barriers, but also makes it difficult to shot at moving enemies at different height.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Twylyte-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Wicked Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virus.zip</path>
		<name>Virus</name>
		<desc>Aliens have infested Earth, and are spreading a deadly virus throughout the planet. Needless to say, they must be stopped, and fast. The time pressure (your score upon completing a level is based on the uninfected percentage of the land) is only one difficult aspect of this shooter.

Viewed in remote 3D with a patchwork-quilt type ground effect, with trees sticking out and full gravity. Controlling your spaceship involves balancing the direction and height as well as thrusting to the right speed. A scanner tells you where the aliens are.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addictaball.zip</path>
		<name>Addicta Ball</name>
		<desc>Addicta Ball is a Breakout clone with a twist. Players control a paddle to break down a wall of different block by bouncing a ball against them, but instead of removing them to clear a level, players need to make a path for the paddle to pass through. As time goes on, the bricks move lower down the screen so the path needs to be created as long as there is an opportunity. The game is over when the bricks hit the paddle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alligata Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Alligata</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advanced Fruit Machine Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>Advanced Fruit Machine Simulator</name>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vindicators.zip</path>
		<name>Vindicators</name>
		<desc>The Tangent Empire are preparing to attack the earth with their convoy of tanks, and it is you who has been sent forward to destroy the 14 space stations which make up the potential invasion threat.

There are 3 sub-levels on each station, which can be played in any order. The action scrolls in every direction, with you guiding your tank-link droid around to shoot the opposition droids. The tank takes a while to steer, making it initially harder to avoid contact with those enemies. Each level contains energy stars, which can be traded in for upgrades such as improved weapons and extra speed after each level.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari Info</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turbo OutRun.zip</path>
		<name>Turbo Outrun</name>
		<desc>The sequel to OutRun features similar basic gameplay to the original, with the action viewed from behind the car, and the challenge being to complete each stage within the time limit. Contact can cause the car to spin, slow down or even flip; in each case you will lose time.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Burger Man.zip</path>
		<name>Burger Man</name>
		<desc>Burger Man is a straight BurgerTime variant. In each of the one-screen levels the player needs to assemble a certain number of burgers. Each burger consists of four parts which lie on the platforms. The player needs to walk over those parts and then they fall down one level - when they meet another of the parts, it also falls down. A burger is done when all four parts are on the lowest level. The platforms are interconnected with ladders which are also the only way to evade the enemies which walk around the levels (the player character can't jump). Touching an enemy results in death.</desc>
		<developer>Cloud Nine Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Byte Back</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Probe.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Probe</name>
		<desc>A long time after the Human Race left Earth and traveled to the Solar System of Sol, some thoughts about returning to Earth came up. As aliens occupied the abandoned earth, The ?Council of the Confederation of Human Kind? decided to send a ship to Earth to conquer the home planet again.

Of course, the player takes control of that Battle Probe and fights his way through 65 levels to expel the aliens by simply killing all of them in this vertical scrolling shoot 'em up game.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Battle Probe-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capital Software Designs Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Crysys</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tintin on the Moon.zip</path>
		<name>Tintin on the Moon</name>
		<desc>Hergé's famous cartoon character is brought to life in this multi-stage action game, specifically based around the episode of the same name. In many details the story was similar to the real moon landings, then many years off.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Roadwars.zip</path>
		<name>Roadwars</name>
		<desc>In Road Wars you are set charging up a long hilly road, trying to make a road safe after a protection malfunction. Crucially, this involves shooting out the barriers at the side of the road (and avoiding falling into the gaps they create). You always play against another droid, who can be treated as friend or foe - pushing them into the gap at the side you've just created is a particularly neat trick, especially when playing a human opponent.

You are armed with a laser gun, which can be directed seperately from your main direction of motion. The roads include a range of hazards, including barriers and spikes, although bonus weaponry and a speed-up can be gained. Contact with these (or your opponent) will gradually drain your shields, and once these are gone you have little chance of surviving for long.</desc>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arcadia Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arcticfox.zip</path>
		<name>Arctic Fox</name>
		<desc>In 2005, aliens have taken over Antarctica. You are sent in to combat them with the new super tank, the Slye-Hicks MX-100, Codename: Arcticfox. 

Arcticfox is a futuristic-based 3D tank simulation game where your overall goal is to destroy the invading aliens' main fortress before Arcticfox is destroyed.

Enemy targets come in all sorts of shapes and sizes: planes, tanks, recon sleds and other important targets such as communication towers, atmosphere converters, etc. Your state-of-the-art killing machine is equipped with a cannon, guided missiles and mines at your disposal in addition to radar and forward/aft view-screens to detect your enemy advances.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dynamix</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Future Basketball.zip</path>
		<name>Future Basketball</name>
		<desc>One of the first Speedball clones takes the basic court layout of basketball as its inspiration. There are 5 players on each team, on a small court with 2 and 3 point shooting areas. The difference is that physical contact of a fairly violent nature is allowed, and the court is littered with mines and bombs to wound the players. Shooting involves holding down fire to get the height right, so avoid being tackled as you prepare your shot. Other basketball rules such as double-dribbling and the 25-second hand-over are unsurprisingly waived. A 3-division league is included to progress through.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Evil 3, The</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-Out.zip</path>
		<name>X-Out</name>
		<desc>In principle, this is yet another (technically very impressive) horizontally scrolling shoot-'em-up. The interesting twist about the scenario is that it doesn't play in space like the similar game R-Type and most of its clones - instead, the fight between good and evil is underwater.

Through five levels, you have to shoot countless enemies, complete with the obligatory mid-level and end-level bosses. The most innovative part of this game comes after a level when you get to purchase new weapons - instead of simply buying upgrades, you can customize your ship by placing your new weapons anywhere on it.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Matrix Marauders.zip</path>
		<name>Matrix Marauders</name>
		<desc>Matrix Marauders is a racing game set in the future. The player takes part in the ultimate racing championship and, well, races against other cars and tries to be the first at the goal. All cars are equipped with weapons which can be used to destroy the opposition. Other things to keep in mind are holes on the track which need to be jumped over and power ups which offer advantages when picked up, e.g. more speed. Permission to start at the next race is only given if the player finishes the race among the first three. Between races the car and its weapon system can be upgraded.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psyclapse</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paperboy.zip</path>
		<name>Paperboy</name>
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, the object of Paperboy is to deliver papers to your customers while inflicting as much damage as possible to the houses of your non-customers. To make things more difficult, numerous obstacles get in your way including construction workers, rogue tires, skateboarders, dogs and cats, cars, and even the occasional tornado.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Atax.zip</path>
		<name>Atax</name>
		<desc>In the darkest years of the Government's oppressive reign, one man had dared to oppose the system.
His only weapon? A small attack craft called ATAX capable of low level skimming advances on the planet surface.
Flying through hostile terrain and under attack from the Government's Guardians you must reach the gateway, each one guarded by an evil assailant.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ramware</developer>
		<publisher>Eclipse</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./North and South.zip</path>
		<name>North and South</name>
		<desc>Based on the Belgian comic book, "Les Tuniques Bleues", this strategy game allows you to replay the American Civil War from both the North and the South sides.nnnnIn the strategy part of the game, you can move your troops on a map of the US. If two opposing armies enter the same state, the battle is played out in an action sequence. Additional action sequences must be accomplished when capturing an enemy fort or train.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Red Storm Rising.zip</path>
		<name>Red Storm Rising</name>
		<desc>The Soviet Union, under severe pressure after destruction of one of their biggest oil refineries, must secure a new source of oil, and to do that, they must disable the West... which means they must invade Europe and fight NATO to a standstill... And the only way NATO can prevent that from happening is to reinforce their forces with convoys from the US and other countries. 

You are in command of one of the US attack submarines. You must hold the ocean against the Soviet navy at all costs, or the land battle will go badly. Part submarine simulator, part dynamic campaign, and part WW3 simulation, Red Storm Rising is an amazing look at modern warfare.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pandora.zip</path>
		<name>Pandora</name>
		<desc>The generation ship Pandora has been set to infect the Earth with a nasty spore of deadly flowers. You have to stop this ship with the help of all the people on board that are still alive. The only person that can stop the ship is you. When you arrive, you have to get ID from the entry officer, or else you get frazzled by a roof lazer. The time limit to destroy this ship before it begins infesting the Earth with spores is 999 seconds.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PSI Software Designers</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyperbowl.zip</path>
		<name>Hyperbowl</name>
		<desc>Hyperbowl is a one-on-one futuristic sport viewed from above, with a small amount of the rectangular pitch visible at a time. Each player controls one of the 10 available spaceships, each with their own subtle strengths and weaknesses in terms of speed, inertia and fire direction. A scanner shows the positions of both ships and the ball, so that things don't become disorientating.nnnnThe aim is to guide the ball either into a 'goal' in the middle of each end (scoring 2 points) or onto the goal-line elsewhere (scoring one point). The ball can be steered either by hitting it with the ship or by shooting at it with your craft's beam (which does not injure or impede the opposition craft in any way). In either case the ball moves in a semi-random direction similar to the one you directed it in, but can rebound off the plus-shaped divots in the wall unexpectedly.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Binary Design, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time and Magik.zip</path>
		<name>Time and Magik</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mandarin Software</developer>
		<publisher>Level 9 Computing</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silkworm.zip</path>
		<name>Silk Worm</name>
		<desc>Silkworm is a classic horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up based on the 1988 Tecmo arcade game. The main difference between this game and many other side-scrolling shoot-em-ups is that you got to be on land as well as in the air.

Player 1 would play as a helicopter, but if a second player joined the game, they would play as a jeep. Both players would have to protect each other as well as themselves. After a certain number of kills, a "goose" helicopter would form on the screen. If the players managed to destroy it they would get a weapons powerup. This would go on throughout the entire game (a "goose" could appear even during the end of level baddie!).</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien World.zip</path>
		<name>Alien World</name>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>HiTech Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conquests of Camelot - The Search for the Grail.zip</path>
		<name>Conquests of Camelot</name>
		<desc>It is the ninth century, and Camelot, the legendary castle ruled by King Arthur, has fallen under a curse. Famine and drought plague the kingdom because of the love triangle between the king, his wife Gwenhyver, and the knight Launcelot. It appears that only the mysterious Holy Grail can restore Camelot, and three knights - Launcelot, Gawaine, and Galahad - embark on a journey to find it, and soon disappear without trace. King Arthur leaves his castle in search of the missing knights, hoping to locate the Grail as well. His quest takes him to real and mythical locations in England, and later to Jerusalem and other areas of the Holy Land.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra On-Line Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hellraider.zip</path>
		<name>Hellraider</name>
		<desc>You are a commander of HMS Raider, on a daring privateer raid into the extremities of the planet Hell. Your mission is to collect diamonds from this hellish planet. Fly around, collect diamonds and shoot all incoming enemies. 

Only your HMS Raider can collect diamonds. There are four fighters inside your Raider, called Orbitals. You can use them to survey the area and destroy enemies while your mothership keeps collecting diamonds automatically or by another player. If orbital is used, camera follows it, so stay close to Raider if another player is controlling it. It is hard to collect diamonds if can't see them or yourself)</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Frames</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Full Metal Planete.zip</path>
		<name>Full Metal Planete</name>
		<desc>Tie-in of the rather unknown but truly brilliant board game of the same name. Up to four players land on a planet with their motherships, trying to gather as much ore as possible within 24 game rounds.

This almost sounds like a happy, idyllic round of pick-the-flowers... if it wasn't for the truckload of tanks and destroyers that each players happens to have in the cargo area of his mothership. So the players usually spend an equal amount of time picking up ore and bashing their contenders' heads in.

The computer game is an extremely accurate conversion of the board game - virtually every aspect has been taken care of.

What's especially refreshing about this game is that it does not rely on luck - it's pure strategy. The only semi-random thing are the tides (high tide, low tide, and something inbetween) which can strand boats and engulf tanks, but even they can be partially predicted.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ludodelire</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SideWinder.zip</path>
		<name>Sidewinder</name>
		<desc>This vertically scrolling shoot 'em up varies from the standard for this style of game, as it also features a degree of horizontal scrolling. The screen area moves across as you reach the edge of the screen and reveals a whole new range of enemies. These include lots of static turrets as well as cannon-fodder waves of enemies.

There are 6 levels and each level starts and ends with you travelling through a tunnel, and emerging on the other side faced with a new graphical setting, be it industrial, space or woodland. After clearing the last level the tunnel leads back to the first level, so there is no real ending to the game. There are no end bosses, instead each level ends with a more difficult part with a large ground structure and increased enemies and turrets. There are 3 difficulty levels to choose from, and a 2 player mode.

Interestingly, the game was not only released for Amiga and PC, but also as a coin-op  machine for arcades. The arcade version is identical to the Amiga version, the arcade PCB  even contains parts of the Amiga operating system.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Synergistic Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronics</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./500cc Grand Prix.zip</path>
		<name>Grand Prix 500cc</name>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Microïds</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T202654</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Steel.zip</path>
		<name>Steel</name>
		<desc>The space ship Steel is so advanced that it is completely operated by robots. As usually in video games, these robots went havoc and have to be put out of business. This job falls to the player who goes on the ship to shut down the security system. He is disguised as robot, but this does not stop the other ones from attacking.</desc>
		<developer>Imperial Software Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kick Off 2 - Winning Tactics.zip</path>
		<name>Kick Off II - Winning Tactics [Data Disk]</name>
		<desc>Winning Tactics is a collection of tactics for Kick Off 2, Kick Off 2: The Final Whistle and Player Manager. There are ten Double Tactics available for The Final Whistle and ten Single Tactics for Kick Off 2 and Player Manager. There are a variety of tactics for attacking, defending, setting an Off Side trap in the Final Whistle and to deal with desperate situations for instance attacking when the ball is lost or defending a slender lead against a strong opponent.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Kick Off 2 - Winning Tactics-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anco</developer>
		<publisher>Anco Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Futebol</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Enterprise.zip</path>
		<name>Enterprise</name>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strider.zip</path>
		<name>Strider</name>
		<desc>The year is 2089AD. In Russia, the evil Grand Master Meio has begun his insane plot to take over the universe. A lone figure drops from a stealth glider into Meio's base. He is Hiryu, Super A-Class Strider. His mission is to defeat the Grand Master and put an end to his plotting once and for all.

Converted from the classic arcade game, Strider lets you run, jump, perform acrobatics and climb walls and overhangs. You wield a plasma sword, called a Cypher, through 5 levels fighting robots and guards, with mid- and end-level bosses.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dames Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>Dames Simulator</name>
		<desc>Dames Simulator is a computerized version of the famous board game called Checkers. The objective, as in all checkers games, is eat all the enemy pieces, before than the opponent.

In Dames Simulator the player has the opportunity to select the color of his pieces (Black or white), the enemy level (between nine levels), the strategy (Defensive or offensive). The player can also save the game in any moment. During the game, the player has the possibility to use the hint option, for advice on the best move to make.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spitfire 40.zip</path>
		<name>Spitfire 40</name>
		<desc>This flight simulation sets you as a young Spitfire pilot in 1940, when World War 2 is hotting up in the skies over the south of England. The program is viewed from within the cockpit, with the instrument panel viewed by pressing Space. The pilot will have to co-ordinate landing gear, brakes and ruddering, and use a map to navigate and find targets. Loops, rolls and split-S moves are all incorporated in the simulation logic.</desc>
		<developer>Eigen Software</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kick Off 2 - Return to Europe.zip</path>
		<name>Kick Off 2 - Return to Europe</name>
		<desc>Return to Europe is a data disk for Kick Off 2 that allows the player to participate in three major European Competitions: the UEFA Cup, the Cup Winners Cup and the European Cup. This was topical in the UK, as English clubs had just been readmitted into Europe, having been banned for several years following the Heysel stadium disaster of 1985.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Anco</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Futebol</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chess Player 2150.zip</path>
		<name>Chess Player 2150</name>
		<desc>Chess Player 2150 is a chess program which played well against the other chess programs of the day and won the 1989 British Open Personal Computer Chess Championship (according to a post in ST Report International Online Magazine, November 13, 1992, No.8.45).  The author was not shy about his program's prowess.  Built into the program is a pull-down menu, giving it's performance against Chessmaster 2000, Chessmaster 2100 and Colossus X, in 10 games apiece.

The game was designed to improve as it played, so over time a game that played against good players would be much better than when it first began.  Users have the option of saving, so that the gained intelligence isn't lost.

Although the author clearly wanted the game to be used by serious chess players, he included whimsical chess pieces as well.  One set includes farm animals (sheep pawns, dog rooks, horse knights, chicken bishops, cow queens, and pig kings); Another setting includes Science-Fiction pieces that look like aliens. The game can be played in 2D or 3D, and includes digitised speech on the Amiga version.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oxford Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>Oxford Softworks</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turbo GT.zip</path>
		<name>Turbo Gt</name>
		<desc>In the game you are a racer on the circuit with three other racers. Entire track is visible on the playscreen and gameplay is flowed in top-down view. You may turn left or right, and accelerate your car, which drives much faster than other cars. Finishing 5 laps on each track of different shape, players must come in first to participate in next race. Otherwise, the game will be over. Sometimes your car can be immobilized for the rest of the race.

The game is available for 1 or 2 players. In 2 players mode one player should use keyboard and another player should use joystick to play simultaneously,  while in 1 player mode player may choose between the controllers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ere Informatique</developer>
		<publisher>Ere Informatique</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./HardBall!.zip</path>
		<name>Hardball</name>
		<desc>Hardball is a baseball action game for one or two players. You can throw a variety of pitches from fast balls to curve balls, steal bases, select team members, and substitute players as the game is played.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Accolade</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Barbarian - The Ultimate Warrior.zip</path>
		<name>Barbarian</name>
		<desc>Barbarian: The Ultimate Warrior is a fighting game that supports one or two players. Players assume the roles of sword-wielding barbarians, who battle in locales such as a forest glade and a "fighting pit". The game's head-to-head mode lets a player fight against another or the computer in time-limited matches. The game also features a single-player story mode, which comprises a series of plot-connected challenges.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Palace</developer>
		<genre>Luta</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stryx.zip</path>
		<name>Stryx</name>
		<desc>You star as half-robot operative Stryx. Dome City is under attack by KILLER CYBORG ASSASSINS! You navigate Stryx through numerous levels on foot, hovercrafts and some weird round eyeball-type flying craft. It's basic side scrolling action/arcade whackiness. This game was released for IBM PC, Amiga and Atari ST systems.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psyclapse</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ThunderCats.zip</path>
		<name>Thundercats</name>
		<desc>This license of the children's TV show set it as a Ghosts 'N Goblins-style hack-n-slash adventure. The Thundercat must defeat Mumm-Ra's forces, which range from dwarves to bats. Although you start with only a sword, more can be collected by attacking the various containers through the levels - later weapons can destroy these enemies quicker, and allow attacks from a distance. Reaching the end of each level sees bonuses for time and kills. The path through the game can be varied on later levels, so you can play it through more than once and find new sections, even though the individual levels only scroll left-to-right.</desc>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gargoyle Games</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BMX Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>BMX Simulator</name>
		<desc>This is an overhead-viewed racing game similar in style to Super Sprint. There are 7 courses of increasing difficulty, incorporating ramps and bumps which significantly affect the bike's handling. Each course has a time limit you must complete 3 laps of the course within, or it's game over. The further inside the time limit you are, the more points you score.

There's a computer opponent, but the scoring isn't affected by whether you beat him just so long as you qualify. There is a two-player mode. A unique feature at the time is the action replay, which can be viewed in slow motion.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King's Quest III - To Heir is Human.zip</path>
		<name>King's Quest 3</name>
		<desc>King's Quest III: To Heir is Human is an adventure game similar in basic gameplay mechanics to its predecessor The player navigates Gwydion with arrow keys and interacts with the environment by typing verb and noun combination commands. Llewdor consists of interconnected screens that loop once the player character reaches the border of the land. Throughout the course of the game, Gwydion will also travel to other locations and have a magic map at his disposal, allowing him to teleport to different areas.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disc.zip</path>
		<name>Disc</name>
		<desc>Disc is a game of fast reflexes and clever thinking. You control one player against the computer or another person. The objective is to finish off your opponents by knocking him off the platforms or by making the platform disappear by hitting the walls behind your opponents. Your weapon is a disc, which you can throw at your opponent or at the walls. The disc will ricochet off the walls, opening a wide range of angles and attacks. You can also try a direct hit at your opponents, as enough of these will eliminate him as well, but be careful - since it gives him a chance to block your disc, thus gain control of it!
As you progress through the levels, from Novice, through Disciple, up to a Great Guide, your rivals become tougher, platforms take longer hits to disappear, and there are more discs on the playing field.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Loriciels</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciels</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Seven Gates of Jambala, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Seven Gates of Jambala</name>
		<desc>The Seven Gates of Jambala is a Jump &amp; Run game. Business with people to come continues, really tough mystery to escape from Jambala. Beware of the mystery traps, the doors behind which the player know not what. Some items will guarded and the player must destroy the big boss in order to get it.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thalion Software GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainment Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Erik.zip</path>
		<name>Erik</name>
		<desc>Erik is a platform game that scrolls vertically but not horizontally. The titular hero is a friendly viking whose peaceful living is disrupted when the evil god Loki is reincarnated. Not happy with Erik's refusal to join the pursuits of more violent vikings, Loki casts a spell on the lands turning the world into a terrible place. Erik's now has to overcome all the dangers so that he once again can live in peace.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Confused Pelican Software</developer>
		<publisher>Atlantis Software Limited</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Demoniak.zip</path>
		<name>Demoniak</name>
		<desc>Demoniak is an interactive fiction adventure in which the player guides four superheroes in an attempt to stop the evil Demoniak entering our dimension and doing dastardly things by sealing his gateway.nnnnThe player may 'become' another character at any time and give that character instructions, objects, such as weapons, may be passed from one character to another.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Palace</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cartoon Capers.zip</path>
		<name>Cartoon Capers</name>
		<desc>Cartoon Capers is the perfect combination of bone-crunching combat and side-splitting humour - and it's suitable for all ages. Throw custard pies, blow up your opponents with a well-aimed bomb, lure him under a one-ton weight, beat him senseless with a lethal punch and body kick, and much more besides in this addictive one or two-player extravaganza.
Using oodles of sampled sound effects, lashings of high-quality cartoon-style graphics and a potentially deadly dose of humour, this stunning game should carry a Government health warning!</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Mandarin Software</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chuckie Egg.zip</path>
		<name>Chuckie Egg</name>
		<desc>In the game you play Hen House Harry who has to collect 12 (a dozen) eggs from each level, while avoiding the ducklings.  The levels each occupy a single screen, and are made up of platforms, ladders and lifts (or elevators), and are thus similar to those in classic platform game Donkey Kong.  Corn can also be collected, which stops the time limit from ticking down and also stops the bonus, collected when the level is completed, from decreasing.  The ducklings also eat the corn, however.

There are only 8 distinct levels.  The ninth level is a copy of level 1, the tenth is a copy of level 2, and so on.  However, on the second time around the ducklings that can use the platforms and ladders are replaced by the Mother Duck, who can fly around the level going through the platforms and ladders.  On the third time around, you have to face both the Mother Duck and the ducklings, and similarly on subsequent goes round, when there are more ducklings.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A&amp;J Software</developer>
		<publisher>Pick &amp; Choose Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Backgammon Royale.zip</path>
		<name>Backgammon Royal</name>
		<desc>Gamão Royale é uma simples versão computadorizada do clássico jogo de tabuleiro de azar &amp; habilidade chamado "Backgammon". Gamão Royale permite ao jogador escolher entre dois estilos de jogo (agressivo ou defensivo), e também selecionar a velocidade do jogo entre três parâmetros (rápido, médio ou lento). O jogo tem uma opção de salvar / carregar que dá ao jogador a oportunidade de continuar o jogo mais tarde.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oxford Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>CP Software</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alternate Reality - The City.zip</path>
		<name>Alternate Reality - The City</name>
		<desc>In Alternate Reality: The City, you are one of many people who have been abducted from earth by aliens and transported to an alternate dimension where you are dumped in a strange, yet familiar city. Your quest is to explore the city, and find the clues that will lead you to your captors and help you get back home.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Datasoft</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stone Age.zip</path>
		<name>Stone Age</name>
		<desc>Stone Age is a challenging puzzle game where you are in control of a dinosaur and you have to make him reach the exit of each cave. The dinosaur can only walk on certain blocks on the level: some are just ordinary blocks, some are movable in the direction the arrow points, some crumble after you walk on them, and some have coloured keys which are needed to get past locks of the same colour.

The game has two difficulty modes, one giving you more time to complete the levels than the other, and every time you run out of time, you lose a life. The levels are coded so you don't lose your progress when you quit, although you'll lose any score gained.

The graphics are simple and cartoony, and the levels come in a variety of scenarios. The game also includes a Jukebox, which allows you to customize the played tracks much like a playlist editor.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stonehenge Soft Art</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainment Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Passengers on the Wind 2.zip</path>
		<name>Reisende im Wind II</name>
		<desc>Passengers on the Wind II allows players to decide the fate of the heroes and direct all of them so that they reach their aim. Players will discover many locations, directions, and events; and will live different stories according to the directions that he makes the characters take. Everything is controlled using either the keyboard or the joystick.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Passengers on the Wind 2-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon II - The Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon II - The Revenge</name>
		<desc>The lovely Marian was rescued from the clutches of the Black Warriors gang by Billy &amp; Jimmy Lee in the first Double Dragon game, but now the gang has killed her in retaliation of their early defeat. The Dragons must now embark on a mission to avenge her d</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Briga de rua</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kick Off 2.zip</path>
		<name>Kick Off 2</name>
		<desc>The original Kick Off was expanded on in many ways for this sequel. The game now features full tournament modes (although the players on the teams are fictitious) and four different pitches (including an implementation of plastic pitches, whose uneven bounce cause controversy when several British clubs tried them in the 1980s).

Viewed top-down, the controls involve trapping the ball under your foot, giving you time to prepare passes. Running with the ball is tricky at first, as it doesn't stick to your foot the way it did in contemporary football games. Complex moves such as overhead kicks, back-heels and long-range through-ball passes can be completed with practice.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anco</developer>
		<publisher>Anco</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mercenary - Escape from Targ &amp; The Second City.zip</path>
		<name>Mercenary - Escape from Targ &amp; The Second City</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Mercenary - Escape from Targ &amp; The Second City-image.png</image>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Quest II.zip</path>
		<name>Explora II</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infomedia Diffusion</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mean 18.zip</path>
		<name>Mean 18</name>
		<desc>Pebbele Beach and St. Andrews are two of the courses on offer in this golf simulation, released in the early years of 16-bit technology. The three-click control system was used, whereby the first click starts the swing, the second sets the power, and the third sets draw or fade.

Beginner and Expert difficulty options are given - the latter mode has more pronounced draw and fade effects, making the timing of the third click even more crucial. You can also choose between regular and professional tees - in the latter option the distance on the holes is longer, and the computer doesn't choose the best club automatically. Because long drives aren't a crucial aspect of many of the holes, the Begginer/Expert setting is a bigger factor on your likely scoring. A uniquie feature for the day was the course designer, which was quite versatile with practice.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsmiths, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Golfe</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Whirligig.zip</path>
		<name>Whirligig</name>
		<developer>Maelstrom Games</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird (UK)</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Afterburner.zip</path>
		<name>Afterburner</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T182204</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Captain Fizz Meets the Blaster-Trons.zip</path>
		<name>Captain Fizz</name>
		<desc>The Blaster-Trons have invaded the planet Icarus, which is set as 20 levels on top of the last. The people can only be saved if a hero or two step forward and reach each of the 20 lifts in this Gauntlet-style game. Two players is the ideal, as gameplay is simultaneous and only ever fills half the screen for each player. Each level has doors which are locked with colour coded keys, as well as doors which can only be used in one direction, and lots of long corridors and mazy layouts. Both yourself and the aliens are armed with lethal lazers, although you can take several hits before dying.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Papyrus Design Group, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Psyclapse</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cybercon III.zip</path>
		<name>Cybercon III</name>
		<desc>The world is in chaos, due to a computer system which was built to look after the world, but inevitably went wrong and started killing people. Only a few people remain, of which you are one, and your mission is to locate and destroy the Cybercon III computer.

The gameplay involves lots of exploration and puzzling, as you try to enter the complex and destroy or disable the hardware. Getting into the system is made easier by the presence of a secret entrance the computer doesn't know about. The computer has all manner of defences in place, which you can shoot out.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Assembly Line, The</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SAS Combat Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>Sas Combat Simulator</name>
		<desc>This action game is similar to Konami’s arcade game Green Beret. It scrolls from left to right, and the levels include ladders and platforms. A constant stream of enemies face you, and can be dispatched with either your machine gun, or one of your limited (but replenishable) supply of grenades. 

The Codemasters logo appears liberally in the game, representing a variety of bonus items. These include jeeps and tanks which give you much more protection, and smart bombs and rapid fire.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Optimus Software Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game Over II.zip</path>
		<name>Game Over II</name>
		<desc>The Serena Commander have the mission to rescue his companion of expedition captured in Moon 4 of System Sotpok, better known like the world Phantis, an unusual place inhabited by a hostile fauna and exuberant flora.

Phantis is an horizontal shooter (R-Type like), combined with platform arcade levels (Turrican like). You have 24 different enemies to beat throughout 4 phases and 6 levels.

This program has two parts, recorded individually on cassette versions. In order to play the second, it's necessary to discover the access code, which is granted when finishing the first.That procedure was called FX Doble Carga (FX Double Charge), and designed to give more hours of addictive playing.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Game Over II-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Game Over II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dinamic Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warhawk.zip</path>
		<name>Warhawk</name>
		<desc>Warhawk is a vertical-scrolling shooter set in space (its authors were inspired by coin-op arcade game Star Force). The player pilots a laser-armed starfighter flying into an asteroid belt, fighting against enemy starbases and waves of fighters, avoiding mines and meteor showers depleting ship's shields, while hunting for precious power-ups.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Warhawk-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Warhawk-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Proteus Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Silverbird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beach Volley.zip</path>
		<name>Ocean Beach Volley</name>
		<desc>While two boys playing Beach Volley a stranger passes by and give them two the possibility to play around the world for the Beach Volley Cup. They take change and start their first competition in London. The rules are easy, one of the teams has to reach seven points first. When you win you fly to other continents like America, Africa or China to meet your next opponent.

You can play against the computer (cup mode) or a second player.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Beach Volley-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Beach Volley-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Beach Volley-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Choice Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./UMS - The Universal Military Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>The Universal Military Simulator</name>
		<desc>UMS (Universal Military Simulator) attempts to cover the ground of games like Empire and go beyond, simulating almost every aspect of warfare in a realistic manner. Battles can range from ancient history to a science-fiction future, with famed battled such as Gettysburg and the Battle of Hastings built in. The view system operates at multiple levels, from a single unit up to the whole theater.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/UMS - The Universal Military Simulator-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/UMS - The Universal Military Simulator-marquee.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intergalactic Development Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Licensees Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prison.zip</path>
		<name>Prison</name>
		<desc>You are a innocent, who is banished on a planet for a crime you didn´t commit. The planet is devastated by a nuclear war and is used as a galactic prison. There are rumors about a spaceship and so you have to search for 8 parts of the ship.nnnnThe game is a action-adventure with multiple interactions. You have to talk and solve puzzles or fight aliens and roboters.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Prison-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Prison-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Prison-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starblaze.zip</path>
		<name>Starblaze</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Starblaze-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Starblaze-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Starblaze-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Logotron</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Night Walk.zip</path>
		<name>Night Walk</name>
		<desc>Night Walk is 2D side scrolling arcade game in dark fantasy world. The player controls an archer. He must go right, kill and avoid enemies like zombies or bats. He has bow, but he must kneel to shoot. He can jump - and must jump over the low-flying arrows. Game has only one level.nn</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Night Walk-image.png</image>
		<publisher>Alternative Software</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Harrier II.zip</path>
		<name>Space Harrier 2</name>
		<desc>Space Harrier II follows (very closely) in the footsteps of its predecessor and involves you (a Space Harrier) going off to save "Fantasy Land". This combined with the many flashing gaudy colors the game throws at you leads me to believe that it was born out of a bad acid trip.

There are 13 stages to complete by jetting around and blasting bad guys and bosses as they approach. The game is played from behind the main character and the landscape rushes up in 3D similar to the effect used in many car games such as Outrun.

The game uses many of the enemies and bosses from the first Space Harrier, but adds an array of new ones as well.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Space Harrier II-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Space Harrier II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Space Harrier II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Space Harrier II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainment Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rotor.zip</path>
		<name>Rotor</name>
		<desc>You control a battle tank (the Rotor) which hovers in a 2D-labyrinth. Gravity pulls heavily on the Rotor, making it fall towards the ground. As any contact with walls or enemies is deadly, your main task is to avoid that. You may rotate your tank freely and accelerate via an afterburner, thus manoeuvring through the corridors -- imagine a mix of Asteroids and Lunar Lander to get an idea of the physics.

Scattered throughout the 18 different fortresses are boxes. Shoot these open to find either a) Fuel: this will replenish your supply, which is drained by shooting and accelerating. b) Sun crystals: Collect all to finish the mission. c) Bombs. They will explode in 30 to 60 seconds, destroying your ship. You can avoid that by leaving the screen quickly, or by picking the bomb up; this earns you major credits, but your ship drops much faster due to increased weight. d) Pearls. Collecting these advance the upgrade counter by one to three steps; you may activate the current upgrade at any time, which will improve your rotation speed, engine strength, weapon, shield etc. Boxes are emptied by carefully flying very, very close to them and activating a tractor field.

As if gravity and accurate flying wasn't challenging enough, the game also confronts you with various enemies. All of these are immobile and fire in a straight line; the sheer mass of them makes avoiding the bullets a difficult task nevertheless. Apart from turrets, there are attractors and repulsors who'll smash you into walls, and force fields that need to be deactivated by finding and shooting a switch.

The tricky labyrinths together with the short supply of fuel, weight constraints and clever upgrade system make Rotor more a game of tactics and accuracy than arcade action. Wild shooting and careless flying will deplete your fuel in no time; you'll have to progress carefully to discern traps in time.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Rotor-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Rotor-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rotor-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Systematics</developer>
		<publisher>Arcana Software Limited</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystal Castles.zip</path>
		<name>Crystal Castles</name>
		<desc>Bentley Bear is trapped in the Crystal Castles! To get out, he will need to collect all of the gems located throughout the castle. The game is played with an isometric view of the multi platformed castle. When Bentley collects all of the gems on the current castle, he will move on to the next, more difficult castle. Wandering throughout the castles are a wide variety of dangerous creatures, which Bentley should avoid. From time to time, a magic hat will appear. If Bentley collects the hat, he will temporarily be invincible to the castles inhabitants.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Crystal Castles-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Crystal Castles-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Crystal Castles-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Crystal Castles-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Andromeda Software</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Chess.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Chess</name>
		<desc>Battle Chess is a quite typical chess game, but it comes with a twist: all pieces are represented by small, realistic figures that walk around on the chessboard, and when one piece takes another, they both take part in an animated battle. There is a different animation for each permutation, depending on which pieces are capturing or being captured. You can also play in 2D without animation. 

The game's opening library includes 30,000 different moves, ensuring a variety of games will unfold across the 10 skill levels. 

Multi-player support can be extended to modem and/or serial port play.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Battle Chess-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Battle Chess-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Battle Chess-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Raffles.zip</path>
		<name>Raffles</name>
		<desc>An eccentric old millionaire stored all his gems and money in odd places around his mansion. When he dies, his widow is unable to find any of this, so she hires master thief Devon Aire to look in the places his criminal mindset suggests it will be stored.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Raffles-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Raffles-marquee.png</marquee>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Softek</developer>
		<publisher>Edge, The</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trauma.zip</path>
		<name>Trauma</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Trauma-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Trauma-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Metal Hurlant</developer>
		<publisher>ERE</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starquake.zip</path>
		<name>Starquake</name>
		<desc>As BLOB, the Bio-Logically Operated Being, you are sent into an unstable planet and charged with the task of preventing it from exploding. This involves collecting various items (the exact combination is different every time you load the game) and taking them to the planet's core.

The game is an arcade adventure viewed from the side, with 512 screens arranged in a 16x32 pattern. A teleport system exists, so once you find the codes you can get quick access to different parts of the game.

The creatures to avoid are intelligent, getting tougher to predict as you get closer to the centre, but you are armed with a gun and can also try to avoid them. BLOB has a set of platforms which can be used to allow limited vertical movement, but these disappear after a few seconds each use.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Starquake-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Starquake-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<developer>Mandarin Software</developer>
		<publisher>Bubble Bus Software</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./East vs. West Berlin 1948.zip</path>
		<name>Berlin 1948</name>
		<desc>Shortly after the war, several countries want to control Berlin. An atomic bomb has been smuggled into the city by the Americans. You play an American spy, whose mission is to guard this bomb and not to let Stalin have it under any circumstances.

This is one of the early examples of a 3rd person perspective point &amp; click adventure, the interface being slightly more complicated than the famous SCUMM system.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/East vs. West Berlin 1948-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/East vs. West Berlin 1948-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/East vs. West Berlin 1948-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Time Warp Software GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Deep.zip</path>
		<name>The Deep</name>
		<desc>In The Deep the player takes the role of a ship which has to defend itself against a variety of underwater enemies, e.g. u-boats or jellyfish with weapons. All the enemies launch missiles or mines at the boat which can be dodged by moving left or right. Water bombs can be dropped to get rid of the enemies - but there are only eight available which slowly refill over time.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/The Deep-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/The Deep-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/The Deep-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Emerald Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Another World.zip</path>
		<name>Another World</name>
		<desc>San Francisco 2016. A series of earthquakes has damaged several nuclear power plants, and the subsequent nuclear contamination has forced the survivors to flee underground. Their only hope to get off the continent is to use newly developed matter transporters. However, these transporters require certain types of crystals to work. Since men cannot survive on the surface, the task of collecting the crystals is assigned to a cyborg.

You take control of the cyborg and must collect different types of crystals in a number of side-scrolling levels, while fighting off mutated animals. Your cyborg can jump, shoot and use smart bombs that damage everything on screen. From time to time, extras appear that replenish some of your health or improve your weapon. If your weapon is at maximum power, you can also collect additional smart bombs. 

The main task of each level is to collect crystals and use them in one of the teleporters that can be found at each end of a level.
There are three types of crystals that are used for different purposes. Green crystal teleport you to the other end of a level. Red crystals take you to another level and blue crystals are needed to get to another continent. Usage of the crystals is rather complicated as each crystal has a different charge and they have to be put into the right slot of the teleporters. Not paying attention to the charge may even cause the transporter to explode.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Another World-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Another World-video.mp4</video>
		<thumbnail>./images/Another World-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<developer>X-ample Architectures</developer>
		<publisher>CP Verlag</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tass Times in Tonetown.zip</path>
		<name>Tass Times In Tonetown</name>
		<desc>Your grandfather has invented a device which makes real everything he can see in his dream. All the strange places and creatures he can dream about really exist in an alternate reality. One of those creatures, named Franklin Snarl, traveled through the device to our reality and kidnapped Gramps, teleporting him into the crazy world of Tonetown. He hopes that Gramps will always remain asleep, which assures Snarl's own existence!

Now it's up to you, the hero of the game to travel to the alternate dimension of Tonetown and to rescue your grandfather. You interact with the environment by either typing in commands, or choosing one of the action icons available as interface. The game, therefore, combines text-based interaction with the more modern "point and click" approach.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Tass Times in Tonetown-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Tass Times in Tonetown-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tass Times in Tonetown-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lure of the Temptress.zip</path>
		<name>Lure of the Temptress</name>
		<desc>The medieval town of Turnvale has fallen into the hands of the evil sorceress Selena. She is controlling an army of an orc-like warrior race Skorl, who serve her with devotion. The Skorl hate humans and have terrorized the town and the nearby land. Diermot is an ordinary fellow who was captured by the Skorl and thrown into prison. His first task will be to escape. After gaining his freedom, Diermot will also have to find out how to liberate his entire homeland from the clutches of the villains.

This adventure game utilizes a special system called Virtual Theater. Non-playable characters will walk around and perform different actions regardless of your interaction with them. There is a variety of options and commands, including the possibility of interaction with a supporting character, whom you can give orders in order to solve some of the game's puzzles.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Lure of the Temptress-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Lure of the Temptress-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Lure of the Temptress-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Lure of the Temptress-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Revolution Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5th Gear.zip</path>
		<name>5th Gear</name>
		<desc>The aim is to drive from the beginning of the track to the end while avoiding obstacles and eliminating (with your machine gun) other vehicles. The tracks are not roads, but maze-like obstacle courses in the wilderness. It is part maze solving, part combat, part racing against the clock.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/5th Gear-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/5th Gear-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/5th Gear-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fantastic Four</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metro-Cross.zip</path>
		<name>Metro-Cross</name>
		<desc>Simple side-scrolling game, where you play a skater who has to pass a set of obstacles in order to reach the end of the level.

You can skate up or down in the screen, or even jump, to be safe from the pipes you encounter on the way. As the game progresses, obstacles are more frequent and more challenging, but the essence is the same. Timing is everything in this game.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Metro-Cross-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Metro-Cross-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Metro-Cross-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resolution 101.zip</path>
		<name>Resolution 101</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Resolution 101-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Resolution 101-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Resolution 101-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Astral Software</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deja Vu - A Nightmare Comes True!.zip</path>
		<name>Deja Vu</name>
		<desc>Déjà Vu: A Nightmare Comes True!! is the first game made by ICOM, known for its adventure games such as Shadowgate and Uninvited. It featured mouse support, a multi-window interface, and bitmapped graphics at a time when text-based interactive fiction was the norm.nnnnIn Deja Vu, action takes place in Chicago in December 1941. Your character's name is Theodore "Ace" Harding - a retired boxer working as a private eye. He wakes up in a toilet stall of a sleazy pub with no memory of who he is or what he is doing there. To make matters worse, you as him soon stumble upon a very dead corpse upstairs with three bullets buried in him. Sure enough, you find there's a gun in your pocket with three bullets missing. From there you have to figure out what happened and who you are before whatever is happening to your brain turns you into a mindless vegetable. To make matters worse the cops would very much like to have a word with you about that stiff.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Deja Vu - A Nightmare Comes True!-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Deja Vu - A Nightmare Comes True!-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Deja Vu - A Nightmare Comes True!-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Class Leader Board.zip</path>
		<name>World Class Leader Board</name>
		<desc>Before the long-running Links series, Access produced the Leader Board lineage, which concludes here. Wind, snap and power are the main considerations as you dodge the bunkers, water and rough which make for more complex courses than the 8-bit versions of the original.

A course editor is provided.  The courses provided include real courses like St. Andrews, a fictional designs such as The Gauntlet, which as the name suggests is designed to push your skills to the maximum.

The PC version revolutionized the use of the PC speaker to reproduce voice samples via their patented "RealSound" process. Quips like "No doubt about it, he's deep in the sandtrap", "Straight onto the fairway", and "Looks like he hit the tree, Jim." are used to provide running commentary on the gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/World Class Leader Board-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/World Class Leader Board-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/World Class Leader Board-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Access Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>8+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chase.zip</path>
		<name>Chase</name>
		<desc>In Chase the player takes the role of a hero who has to save the abducted princess Chardonnay. To do so, the hero mans a space ship and has to solve four levels with slightly different gameplay mechanics</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Chase-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Chase-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chase-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Barker, T.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaxy Force II.zip</path>
		<name>Galaxy Force II</name>
		<desc>You are strapped into a spaceship to take on five dangerous settings, ranging from a pleasant garden to hostile fire and tough ice. You will have to fly freely before cutting through tunnels and canyons, and finally destroying an alien base. Your energy read out starts at 1200 and decreases as shots hit you, or you make contact with a wall or blockage. You have infinite cannons and guided missiles to help you along. You can get regular energy recharges and power upgrades, by shooting and then collecting their carrier pods.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Galaxy Force II-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Galaxy Force II-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Galaxy Force II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Galaxy Force II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM R&amp;D Dept. #2</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strike.zip</path>
		<name>Strike</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Strike-image.png</image>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mission Genocide.zip</path>
		<name>Mission Genocide</name>
		<desc>Your mission is to fly over the Bad Star Empire in your star fighter and destroy as much of their world as you can in response to them attacking and devastating your planet CRYS-CIT. The more damage you inflict on their fighters and installations means the less chance they will attack again and finally destroy your planet.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Mission Genocide-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Mission Genocide-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mission Genocide-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Drinksoft</developer>
		<publisher>Silverbird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Untouchables, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Untouchables</name>
		<desc>You are The Untouchables in this side-scrolling action game. Play as Elliot Ness after the ruthless Mafia boss Al Capone. You have various tasks throughout the six levels and a variety of weapons to pick up such as a shotgun or tommy gun. Watch out for Capone’s henchmen though.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Untouchables, The-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Untouchables, The-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Untouchables, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Untouchables, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Special FX Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Atomix.zip</path>
		<name>Atomix</name>
		<desc>Atomix is a puzzle game. On each level, you are given a couple of atoms, and your task is to arrange them into a specific shapes. 

In a top-down view, you see all the atoms available for you to move, and all the directions they can connect to. Down below on the left side is a small picture of what you must get. That picture represents some molecular structure that you must complete by moving atoms horizontally and vertically. Once you move your atom, it won't stop unless it bumps into something, so you have to use other atoms as blockades to prevent it from going into unwanted areas. 

There are over 50 levels, and you have limited time for each level.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Atomix-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Atomix-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Atomix-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TaleSoft</developer>
		<publisher>Thalion Software</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Leader Board.zip</path>
		<name>Leader Board</name>
		<desc>When converting the original Leader Board golf simulation to the 16-bit systems, Sculptured took advantage of the power of these systems by adding trees, bunkers and rough, thus increasing the variety of the challenge. The same basic features still exist in terms of shot styles, and in the way a 72-hole contest can be arranged through a variation of the 4 provided 18-hole courses. Hold the left mouse button while moving the mouse to affect shot angle, then use the right button to fire the shot away.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Leader Board-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Leader Board-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Leader Board-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Access Games</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starglider 2.zip</path>
		<name>Starglider 2</name>
		<desc>More space combat and strategy in this sequel, which challenges you to collect the elements to form a bomb to destroy a resistance force, before delivering them through heavy fighting. Each planet has its own characteristics, with differing inhabitants and features. 

As well as flying through space, you must dart through tunnels under the planets, which restricted your movement range but are where most of the weapons are. As you go along you'll have to obtain objects from people, and trade them so as to be able to complete your main objectives.

The biggest advance from the original Starglider was seen as the polygon graphics, which are filled on 16-bit systems, and contain considerable detail.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Starglider 2-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Starglider 2-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Starglider 2-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Wrestling.zip</path>
		<name>Championship Wrestling</name>
		<desc>Arcade-style game about wrestling, featuring 8 different characters, like K.C. Colossus or Prince Vicious, and 25 different moves, like leg drops, spin kicks, body slams, rope bouncing, flying drop kicks and the so-called "infamous" atomic drop. You can even throw your opponent off the ring. Scoring is based on the complexity of your moves.

Two-player hot-seat feature available as well, and up to 8 players can play in the same championship.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Championship Wrestling-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Championship Wrestling-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Championship Wrestling-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tai-Pan.zip</path>
		<name>Tai-Pan</name>
		<desc>You wish to make your fortune in China, in this adaptation of James Clavell's book. First job is to get enough of a loan to buy a ship; once you have this, and get a crew either by paying them or simply kidnapping them, you can begin trading.

The game has 3 main stages, and a number of different gameplay elements, largely allowing you choose your own path. Initially you walk the streets trying to get the right elements and people, then you head out onto the waters to head to other trading cities. Upon approaching other ships you can board them and do battle with their inhabitants.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Tai-Pan-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Tai-Pan-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tai-Pan-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Artificial Dreams.zip</path>
		<name>Artificial Dreams</name>
		<desc>This slow-paced methodical shoot 'em up is viewed from top down, with your ship flying up the screen. The game's levels have a clearly square design to them, with lots of barriers to negotiate as well as aliens (which generally stay in the same vertical plane as they fly towards you).

Many squares featuring a variety of power-up type effects, such as improved weaponry, extra lives, a level warp, a device to stop the landscape's (otherwise constant) scrolling (thereby giving you a chance to 'pick off' the aliens more carefully), and one which speeds up the aliens (avoid this!). You can move backwards a short way, but it takes a few squares' worth of screen to get fully across the screen, so bear this in mind in the mazier sections.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Artificial Dreams-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Artificial Dreams-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Artificial Dreams-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxwell Technology Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Prism Leisure Corporation Plc</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Theme Park Mystery.zip</path>
		<name>Theme Park Mystery</name>
		<desc>Theme Park Mystery is a strange adventure game set in the mysterious world of gypsies, magic and supernatural powers where nothing is quite what it seems. Your routine life is disrupted forever when you use a discarded tokens in the fortunetelling machine.
Use the tokens to get a ticket from the Zoltan Wizard fortune telling machine at the Train Station to journey through the four worlds of Dragonland, Dreamland, Futureland and Yesterdayland.  Find out what drove the fun seekers away and your uncle insane.  Hunt for hidden keys, fiery torches and supernatural potions to help you avenge your uncle's death.  Terror Awaits!</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Theme Park Mystery-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Theme Park Mystery-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Theme Park Mystery-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Joined Up Writing Software</developer>
		<publisher>Image Works</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turrican II - The Final Fight.zip</path>
		<name>Turrican II</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Turrican II - The Final Fight-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Turrican II - The Final Fight-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Turrican II - The Final Fight-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Turrican II - The Final Fight-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</developer>
		<publisher>Factor 5</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tau Ceti.zip</path>
		<name>Tau Ceti</name>
		<desc>A space simulation with elements from a number of other genres mixed in.  Your mission is to destroy a robot army that has taken over a planet.  Gameplay includes arcade sequences, where you fly your ship around and shoot the enemy robots; strategy elements, as you attempt to navigate and locate parts to repair the defense system; and even text-adventure elements, in the form of giving commands to your ship's computer.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Tau Ceti-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Tau Ceti-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tau Ceti-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRL Group</developer>
		<publisher>CRL Group</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Police Quest - In Pursuit of the Death Angel.zip</path>
		<name>Police Quest v2.0g</name>
		<desc>Sonny Bonds is a small town policeman who must fight against the rising tide of drugs in his city. The game is based on real police procedure and adheres carefully to following the rules of police work. Beginning as a patrol officer and working into detectives, Sonny will chase down the infamous Death Angel and put an end to his criminal underworld.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Police Quest - In Pursuit of the Death Angel-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Police Quest - In Pursuit of the Death Angel-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Police Quest - In Pursuit of the Death Angel-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Action Fighter.zip</path>
		<name>Action Fighter</name>
		<desc>This is a top down vertically scrolling shooter, in which you start off as a motorbike. You are quite vulnerable to attack at first, but power ups come in the form of a Sega van which you have to dock with. The first time you dock you get double fire, the second time gives you a rocket, the third gives a rear force field and the fourth invulnerablility.

By destroying cars and bikes that appear on your way, you can collect A-F letters. Collecting A through to D allows you change into a sportscar which is less vulnerable to attack, but not as nimble. Collect all the letters in order to be able to transform into a high tech plane. This is the final stage of one of the five missions. Only the high tech plane can guide you to your destination in which your main target is hiding.

There is also time limit in which you have to complete the mission. It is advisable to transform into the high tech plane as fast as it is possible.

Picking up flags gives you bonus points with 10,000 points gaining you an extra life.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Action Fighter-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Action Fighter-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Action Fighter-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebird</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chess Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>Chess Simulator</name>
		<desc>Chess Simulator is a chess game which offers the standard features: playing chess against the AI which can be set in a number of different levels suited for beginners and advanced players (the maximum ELO rating is 2150); optionally with an advice option which tries to teach chess to the player. Graphical features include a number of different pieces and the option to change the angle and zoom of the 3D playfield. Of course it is also possible to use a top-down perspective. The game also provides a way to calculate the user's ELO score: the program presents 24 situations and the player must provide likely moves within two minutes.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Chess Simulator-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Chess Simulator-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chess Simulator-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Light Corridor, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Light Corridor</name>
		<desc>The aim of the game is to guide a ball through 50 levels of walls, barriers and general obstacles. You control a bat, which must 'serve' the ball into play, and then follow it through the level, deflecting it before it falls behind you, as this costs you one of your 4 lives. Initially the obstacles are all static, but moving barriers add timing, reactions and luck to proceedings.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Light Corridor, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Light Corridor, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Light Corridor, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Test Drive.zip</path>
		<name>Test Drive</name>
		<desc>This mix of racing simulation and arcade game consists of driving a choice of 5 sports cars on a mountain strip at the fastest speed possible without getting caught by the cops.  To avoid them, use your radar detector -- or just try to outrun them if they spot you.  Manual stickshift only, so make sure you don't redline or you'll blow your engine.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Test Drive-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Test Drive-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Test Drive-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Test Drive-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Distinctive Software</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chessmaster 2000, The.zip</path>
		<name>Chessmaster 2000</name>
		<desc>This iteration of the Chessmaster series offers a  strong chess opponent at 12 skill levels, catering for novices to Grandmasters. Its many features include an opening library built around 71,000 moves, and the ability to print out the move history. To help novices there is a teach mode showing all legal moves, a hint move offering what the computer feels is a strong move, and the chance for the Chessmaster to analyse all previous moves in a game. Famous real-life game positions and pre-set challenges offer individual challenges.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Chessmaster 2000, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Chessmaster 2000, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chessmaster 2000, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Software Toolworks</developer>
		<publisher>The Software Toolworks</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wrangler.zip</path>
		<name>Wrangler</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Wrangler-image.png</image>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Manoir de Mortevielle, Le.zip</path>
		<name>Le Manoir de Mortevielle</name>
		<desc>Mortville Manor is an adventure game of Jerome Lange.  In 1951, someone is murdered in an impressive manor and it's up to Jerome Lange to solve the case.  But beware: something otherworldly is going on here...</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Manoir de Mortevielle, Le-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Manoir de Mortevielle, Le-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Manoir de Mortevielle, Le-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lankhor</developer>
		<publisher>Lankhor</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chase H.Q..zip</path>
		<name>Chase HQ</name>
		<desc>As an undercover agent of Chase Headquarters, your job is to patrol the streets and track down five criminals. You are given a mission briefing before you start which gives information on the suspect and what car they drive. Then you drive across the city without crashing into other cars, and catch up with the criminal's car. To arrest the suspects, you must keep bumping into their car until it is no longer functional. And you have to do this under a strict time limit. You can't afford to crash into cars or buildings or you waste time getting on the road again. 

However, once you've caught up with your suspect, you are given more time. Your car is also equipped with turbo boosts, which you can use to gain extra speed if you are way behind the criminal. Each arrest is based on a "suspicion".</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Chase H.Q.-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Chase H.Q.-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Chase H.Q.-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chase H.Q.-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chicago 30's.zip</path>
		<name>Chicago 30's</name>
		<desc>You are Eliot, on the trail of the gangsters who dominate Chicago in the 1930s. They lurk in the docks, on the streets and in an alcohol distillery, armed with guns and grenades, and must be taken out. 

Gameplay is side-view and takes place on a number of vertical levels, with a feel similar to Green Beret. Jump and duck to target and avoid crooks. Later you spend time inside a car, and can lean out of the window to shoot people. Watch out for enemy cars, which can only be destroyed using grenades.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Chicago 30's-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Chicago 30's-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chicago 30's-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Topo Soft</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cloud Kingdoms.zip</path>
		<name>Cloud Kingdoms</name>
		<desc>Baron von Bansai has stolen Terry's precious collection of crystals, and dropped them onto 32 different kingdoms, so Terry sets off to retrieve them. Viewed from above, his challenge sees him having to progress through these worlds, collecting keys to gain access to different sections, and avoiding enemy balls and bugs by jumping them where possible. There are no 'lives' as such, but there's a strict time limit of around 400 seconds for the whole game, and death puts you back to the start of the level, with time lost as well. You get an extra 80 seconds for completing each level though.

The levels feature all manner of further hazards - there are holes in the ground to avoid falling through (some visible, some hidden), arrows which force the ball in a particular direction, slippery squares making any movement's effect exaggerated, magneted squares making it impossible to jump from, and many more. Fortunately lots of power-ups, time boosts and bonus fruits are dropped onto the levels at random intervals as well.

To complete the game you must clear 8 levels, and the structure is non-linear - initially you have a choice of 4 levels, and after completing one of those you have a choice of 4 more levels (which are different depending on which level you completed first). The third and fourth levels you take on as you go through the game are chosen from a choice of 3, the fifth and sixth from a choice of two, and only those final two levels are perscribed (although they do vary depending on which levels you've already done).

Each of the 32 worlds has its own twist - Arrow Kingdom has a large amount of arrows directing you, Ice Kingdom is especially slippery, Unseen Kingdom leaves you to work out the route for yourself (other than the holes, which are all you can see), Box Kingdom involves a lot of flying over some trapped squares to grab the keys they contain before making the main jumps onto the sections which contain crystals, and so on.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Cloud Kingdoms-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cloud Kingdoms-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cloud Kingdoms-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electralyte</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kick Off 2 - The Final Whistle.zip</path>
		<name>Kick Off 2 - Final Whistle</name>
		<desc>The Final Whistle is a data disc for Kick Off 2 that improves the gameplay and adds some new features. Among the features there is new tactics implementation (positioning and movement depends on whether the team is defending or attacking), new corner kicks that give better control of the height, shot power, bias and curling of the ball, improved control of goal kicks and throw ins, additional player attribute Flair that determines whether the player will play a passing or make a solo attempt at the goal, new controls that allows the player to make Flick Balls and Overhead Kicks, choice to play with offside rules, new 2 players team mode, new kits and pitches and if you have an expanded Amiga extra sound effects and improved graphics.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Kick Off 2 - The Final Whistle-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Kick Off 2 - The Final Whistle-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kick Off 2 - The Final Whistle-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Anco</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Futebol</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Manchester United.zip</path>
		<name>Manchester United</name>
		<desc>A football management simulation with an arcade component where you manage the world's most famous football team. Lead them through a season to see how many trophies you can win. You can pick your dream team for the positions you want and see how they do in the championships.

The management side lets you choose and configure your team, choosing training schedules to develop your players and viewing their skills.

The arcade side can be used purely as a hands off simulation, or as a way to have a direct effect on the result.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Manchester United-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Manchester United-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Manchester United-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Manchester United-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lethal Xcess - Wings of Death II.zip</path>
		<name>Lethal Xcess - Wings of Death</name>
		<desc>After the events of Wings of Death, the once evil sorcerer Sagyr has been reintegrated into society and only does good things with his magic. Unfortunately, one day he stumbles upon a curse which releases an evil witch called Xandrilia. She immediately conquers the world and teleports Sagyr 3 000 years into the future. Using a spaceship, his only hope to free the world is to destroy the planet Metallycha, where Xandrilia's heirs live.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Lethal Xcess - Wings of Death II-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Lethal Xcess - Wings of Death II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Eclipse</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Interphase.zip</path>
		<name>Interphase</name>
		<desc>Dreams are made by The Dreamtrack Corporation, a group of evil subliminal-messengers whose intention is to destroy the minds of the minority of people capable of interpreting other people's dreams and live them out through entertainment. That's the story in this distinctly Cyberpunk-inspired title, and you play Chad, the man who discovers this secret, and aims to put an end to it.

Your task on each level is to clear a path for Kaf-E, your girlfriend, to be able to progress to the heart of the Dreamtrack HQ, getting past each of the myriad of security systems they have built up. A map must be used to navigate the route through the systems, with lots of information readily available.

The basic gameplay sees you darting through 3D tunnels using the mouse, and is like a prototype Descent, with your ship kitted out with cannons and missiles, with each enemy better dealt with by one or the other.

As well as ensuring your own survival, you must guide Kaf-E through the levels by blasting out the correct sections to clear a path for her. As she has no intelligence, and simply walks into walls, this element can be compared to Lemmings.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Interphase-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Interphase-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Interphase-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Assembly Line</developer>
		<publisher>Imageworks</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spherical.zip</path>
		<name>Spherical</name>
		<desc>Solomon's Key is a clear conceptual influence for this action puzzler. Our hero must guide a ball through a level to the spot marked 'In', by creating and removing blocks to alter its path. The game is prevented from being a pure clone due to the ball, which moves automatically once activated, and can be controlled by using strategically-placed blocks.

Simply reaching the ball usually involves modifying the level layout using these bricks. There are enemies moving on fixed paths which must be avoided, and bonus items to collect. Also watch for bonuses such as invincibility, gravity-alteration and teleporting. You take time to rotate, so the controls aren't truly immediate. The ball takes 20 seconds to start moving, so use this time to plan ahead.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Spherical-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Spherical-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Spherical-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blazing Thunder.zip</path>
		<name>Blazing Thunder</name>
		<desc>The main character in this old fashioned no frills shoot 'em up is a Rambo doppelganger, which the developers may have been lucky not to be sued over. The main player is surrounded by a large tank which moves around as if you are walking it Flintstones style.

Gameplay follows the usual pattern for Ikari Warriors-style games - kill off the bazooka-toting baddies, which emerge from hiding places or enter the screen in waves. You can do this by either shooting them or running them over with your tank. Parts of the scenery often block your path and need destroying. Once you clear the level you are confronted by a boss, which in the first level is an enormous tank which you have to disable the guns of.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Blazing Thunder-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Blazing Thunder-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Blazing Thunder-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PAL Developments</developer>
		<publisher>HiTech Software</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Mania.zip</path>
		<name>Pacmania</name>
		<desc>Pac-Mania is a variation on the game Pac-Man. You need to guide Pac-Man around a maze and eat all of the dots on the board in order to proceed on to the next round. Numerous, multi-colored ghosts also roam the maze trying to stop you. If you eat one of the power pellets in the maze, the ghosts will temporarily turn blue and run from you. Pac-man can earn bonus points by eating the ghosts when they are in this state. The maze is now in 3-D and is larger than screen which will scroll to follow the action. To help get out of tight spots, Pac-Man now has the ability to jump. But be careful, because some of the ghosts have learned this trick as well and you could end up in a mid air collision!</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Pac-Mania-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Pac-Mania-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Pac-Mania-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pac-Mania-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Grandslam Entertainment Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Teque</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thunder Burner.zip</path>
		<name>Thunder Burner</name>
		<desc>You are a pilot of some robot/spacejet transformer on some deserted planet full of cacti and enemy ships. You may turn left/right at the angle of 45 degrees, move at the angle of 45 degrees, accelerate/decelerate speed of your moving, shoot, and metamorphose into a spacejet at will. During 12 levels of gameplay enemies fly towards you, and you should shoot them or avoid them, because each meeting with the enemy means decreasing the number of instances of your transformer. You'll also need to collect spheres to maintain your fuel levels. When all instances of your spacejet will be lost you may be enlisted in the High Score Table.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Thunder Burner-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Thunder Burner-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Loriciels</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciels</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Future Wars - Time Travellers.zip</path>
		<name>Future Wars - Time Travellers</name>
		<desc>In the year 1989, a simple window cleaner is working outside of a skyscraper. Intending to play a prank on his angry boss, the unlikely hero discovers a secret passage leading to a time machine along with mysterious alien documents. Operating the device transports the protagonist to the year 1304, where he is given a seemingly ordinary task of rescuing a lady in danger. However, he soon finds out about a much more serious threat of a global alien invasion. The hero has to travel to the remote future of the 44th century and eventually to the even more remote past of the Cretaceous period to foil their plans.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Future Wars - Time Travellers-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Future Wars - Time Travellers-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Future Wars - Time Travellers-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Future Wars - Time Travellers-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delphine Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Delphine Software International</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowgate.zip</path>
		<name>Shadowgate</name>
		<desc>Using the same graphical interface as Deja Vu, Shadowgate is an adventure game set in a fantasy world. Players take the part of an adventurer sent to the ancient keep of Shadowgate on a quest to find a mystic artifact known as the Staff of Ages and stop the evil Warlock Lord from summoning a horrific demon known as the Behemoth. However Shadowgate has become infested with the Warlock Lord's demonic minions, not to mention the castle's still functional booby-traps.

Unlike Deja Vu, death comes at you suddenly, unexpectedly, and most of all OFTEN. Such simple acts as pulling the wrong switch or opening the wrong door can cause you to be skewered by a booby-trap or disemboweled by a monster. It's allso worth mentioning the fact that if your torch burns out (this happens quite regularly) and you forget to light a new one, you'll trip in the dark and break your neck.

A Windows 3.x update to this game was created in 1991.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Shadowgate-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Shadowgate-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Shadowgate-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Icom</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hostages.zip</path>
		<name>Hostages</name>
		<desc>Terrorists have overrun an embassy and hold the people inside as hostages. You control six counter-terrorists whose mission is to eliminate the terrorists. In the first part of the game, you have to bring three men into position so they can snipe the building. The second part involves entering the building with the other three men to kill the terrorists and rescue the hostages. Depending on how well you positioned your snipers, you can use them to assist you on that mission.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Hostages-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Hostages-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hostages-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toobin'.zip</path>
		<name>Toobin'</name>
		<desc>Toobin' involves Biff and Jet racing their way down the rapids of a river, riding on tires. You rotate your tyre left or right, and drift as the current sends you, making sure to avoid the banks of the river, and the dividing lines in the middle. Hazards include crocodiles, stray logs and branches, and fishermen - you are armed with a limited supply of tin cans to take care of these. There are gates to slide through on the way down - these give you a points bonus. Each level has a strict time limit to adhere to, although there's a kickin' party at the end if you succeed.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Toobin'-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Toobin'-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Toobin'-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gravity.zip</path>
		<name>Gravity</name>
		<desc>Gravity is an isometric-perspective action game whose gameplay centers around maneuvering a spaceship around a three-dimensional isometric grid in an attempt to colonise planets. Centers of gravity create "pits" on that grid, which are the basic obstacles to maneuver around.
An alien species called "Outies" plans on transforming all suns of the galaxy into black holes. They feed off raw energy, and as black holes are a good source of that, they attempt to create as many as possible of them. The player is sent out in a scout ship to colonise worlds in an attempt to gain resources to use for battling the Outies.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Gravity-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gravity-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wyvern (The)</developer>
		<publisher>Image Works</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./James Pond - Underwater Agent.zip</path>
		<name>James Pond - Underwater Agent</name>
		<desc>"James Pond" is (obviously) a parody on the famous agent 007 stories. You control Pond, a fish-like creature, who has to complete several missions, while making his way through levels full of dangers and hostile creatures. It is not a typical "jump and run" game: instead of breezing through large levels, Pond has to complete unique missions for each game area: free hostages, detonate a structure, find keys, etc. It is possible to exit a level only after having completed the objective. Many missions are timed.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/James Pond - Underwater Agent-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/James Pond - Underwater Agent-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/James Pond - Underwater Agent-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vectordean</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tower of Babel.zip</path>
		<name>Tower Of Babel</name>
		<desc>The Zapper, Pusher and Grabber robots were dropped onto the planet of the Shinerians, but are now desperate to return home. They have killed off the Shinerian race, but must climb a high tower, negotiating all the traps it holds, before they can contact their masters.

Each robot's name indicates what their main function and purpose is, and these skills must be combined for success. Each section has its own task - collecting energy pods and destroying mines and bombs for example. The creatures which fill the towers must be avoided, or used to your advantage.

The game is viewed through a rotating camera with variable zoom, giving the game an advanced 3D feel for the day. A level designer has also been included.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Tower of Babel-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Tower of Babel-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tower of Babel-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starglider.zip</path>
		<name>Starglider</name>
		<desc>The Planet Novenia has been attacked by the Egrons, who snuck in by disguising their craft as the protected Starglider species, which Novenia's automated defenses were programmed not to shoot. 

Your task is to fight them off using only an obsolete Airborne Ground Attack Vehicle. This was designed as the ultimate combat machine, with sophisticated hardware up to Draziw Yarg's high standards. It has a fully-rechargeable shield, plasma drive unit, an inbuilt scanner and 10,000-sector map, a top speed of 2550 Urads and two homing missiles.

The game is viewed from within AGAV's cockpit, with control over speed, weapon targeting and firing. There are several control options to decide exactly how the craft works, with fixed or floating sighting, and the option of automatic centering, allowing you to balance the game between easy sighting and advanced shooting ranges.

Repair depots must be visited frequently, as they can refill the weapon bays as well as repairing the ship. Crucially, the Egron Stargliders need 3 missiles to shoot down, so at least 1 visit to a depot is required to complete this job, at which point you move up to the next, harder, level.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Starglider-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Starglider-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Starglider-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Missing - One Droid.zip</path>
		<name>Missing- One Droid</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Missing - One Droid-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Bug Byte</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Captain Blood.zip</path>
		<name>Captain Blood</name>
		<desc>Bob Morlock is a game designer who has just developed a new sci-fi video game set in outer space and alien worlds. While testing the product Morlock inexplicably finds himself in the spaceship within the game. A hyperspace accident clones him thirty times. Each of the clones departs, taking with him a portion of a vital fluid that sustains Morlock's life. Assuming the persona of the brave Captain Blood, the programmer tracks down and disintegrated twenty-five clones, spending 800 years to achieve that goal. However, five clones still remain, hidden somewhere in the depths of the galaxy. Captain Blood must find these clones and destroy them before he loses his own life.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Captain Blood-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Captain Blood-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Captain Blood-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exxos</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rock Star Ate My Hamster.zip</path>
		<name>Rockstar Ate my Hamster</name>
		<desc>You are Cecil Pitt, a wannabe rock star manager. You must choose from 1-4 rock stars (with names such as Tina Turnoff and Wacko Jacko) to manage by viewing their audition tapes. Once you chosen your artists you then have to choose what kind of gear to get them - spanking new, second hand or dodgy. The dodgy gear is dirt cheap but you might pay for your choice later on in the game.

To make your group a star, you have options such as practicing, publicity stunts, and buying gifts for your stars. Each action you choose advances the calendar by one day and you have until December to achieve your ultimate aim of superstardom - represented by a line graph which rises or falls depending on the performance of your band's releases.

Once your band has recorded their first album you can choose to release the single and/or the album. The single needs a video to go with it which costs varying amounts of cash depending on which director you choose. You can choose to go for publicity, but this can be risky as there is a chance that one of your rock stars will be in the papers as an ex-rock star who died in any of many strange ways (all that's missing is a 'bizarre gardening accident'). Publicity affects your sales directly and also affects the crowds who attend your gigs. You lose the game if either you run out of money, or all of your rock stars die.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Rock Star Ate My Hamster-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Rock Star Ate My Hamster-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rock Star Ate My Hamster-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pharaoh III.zip</path>
		<name>Pharaoh III</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Pharaoh III-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Pharaoh III-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Supernova</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hacker II - The Doomsday Papers.zip</path>
		<name>Hacker 2</name>
		<desc>Hacker II: The Doomsday Papers is a real-time strategy game. It is the sequel to Hacker.

Once again you hack into a computer system, just to end up saving the world. Hacker II: The Doomsday Papers opens with the console to the "Actisource" computer hotline system (a nice self-ironic pun - although nobody knows why a serious hacker might want to crack a help service for computer games...). However, your quiet little hack is soon disturbed: The government wants you for a secret mission. It, again, involves a robot drone and you're the one at the remote control. Although this time, it's not the whole globe that's your playground, but a high security facility in Russia, where the plans for global domination are hidden.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Hacker II - The Doomsday Papers-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Hacker II - The Doomsday Papers-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hacker II - The Doomsday Papers-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cricket Captain.zip</path>
		<name>Cricket Captain</name>
		<desc>Cricket Captains have a much greater role than their equivalents in most sports. Most major tactical decisions during the match ultimately come under their control, as they do in this simulation, in which you can play or merely watch the match action. Teams are real but the player names are fictitious.

Your options are quite similar to those of a soccer manager. You must hire a coach, scout and physio to enable you to train your players and keep them fit, and to acquire new ones through the soccer-style transfer market. 

You must select your team of 11 players before the match, with talented all-rounders more common than in real-life. The game takes in the four main tournaments of the time - a single-division league of four-day unlimited-overs matches, the Sunday League of one-day games, and two cup competitions.

The match view features a plan view of the fielding setup, and a forced-perspective view of the batsman as a shot is lined up. You must time and place your shot correctly in order to score off it. When fielding you can choose the bowler and alter the field setup.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Cricket Captain-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Cricket Captain-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Cricket Captain-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>The Majestic 12</developer>
		<publisher>D&amp;H Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Night Shift.zip</path>
		<name>Night Shift</name>
		<desc>Night Shift is a strange platform/puzzle combo of a game. 

Thriving Toy Company seeks energetic employee to operate unconventional machine. Generous rewards in store for you... if you can meet the challenge!

1. Master the BEAST to crank out action figures from Star Wars(r), Indiana Jones(r) and your favourite LucasArts games. You must meet your quota each night.
IF YOU FAIL, YOU'RE FIRED!
Make your quota! Get a raise! Get a bonus! Get a bigger quota!
Fend off nasty lawyers and furry pests.
Make it all the way from the assembly line to the mansion on the hill!

(from the back of the box)

Gameplay is divided into 6 different kinds of shifts, each with its own assignments (provide power, use wrench to tighten bolts, etc.)  You will use tools throughout the game, and will be awarded with bonus items (hourglass for extra time, cash bonus for extra points).</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Night Shift-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Night Shift-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Night Shift-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Attention To Detail</developer>
		<publisher>Lucasfilm Games</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ballistix.zip</path>
		<name>Ballistix</name>
		<desc>Psygnosis' Ballistix is an arcade game in which you have to manipulate a ball in order to score a goal with your opponent. To do this, you will control an arrow that defines a direction, and pressing the fire key will launch a ball from this arrow in the direction the arrow points to; by launching balls at correct angles, you will manipulate the main ball and control the way it moves. Ballistix also keeps certain physics laws (namely gravity and friction), and will present you with varying obstacles in either one or two player mode.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Ballistix-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ballistix-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ballistix-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ballistix-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psyclapse</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flimbo's Quest.zip</path>
		<name>Flimbo's Quest</name>
		<desc>Rescuing girlfriends is a pretty common challenge in older computer games - why can't any of these ladies look after themselves? On this occasion Pearly has been kidnapped by Fransz Dandruff, so you'd better make sure he's hair today, gone tomorrow.

The gameplay is platform based, although you can move down platforms as well as up to the next one. There are lots of baddies (drawn in a cutesy style) who need shooting and offer rewards. the 7 levels are fairly short, relatively easy, and linear.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Flimbo's Quest-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Flimbo's Quest-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Flimbo's Quest-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Flimbo's Quest-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spidertronic.zip</path>
		<name>Spidertronic</name>
		<desc>In Spidertronic the player gets to take control of a robotic spider moving through a world of isometric levels. Each level consists of tiles that make out the spider's web. Problem is that the web is under siege by odd spherical creatures. This has lead to some passageways being broken and now it's up to our little spider to repair the damage done. The aim then is to rebuild these parts of each level so that the spider can move on to the next. This is done with the use of coloured tiles. The HUD shows a flashing dot that indicates what colour is needed. The spider then has to find a tile in that colour and move it to the tile that needs to be repaired. Once this is all done the spider gets access to a teleporter and can move on to the next level. The spider isn't alone however. It has to be careful not to come into contact with the balls that move around the web. Balls can be destroyed by building a web in front of them. They won't be gone for long though since they will respawn after just a few seconds.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Spidertronic-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Spidertronic-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Decroix - Garofalo</developer>
		<publisher>Ere Informatique</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Harrier.zip</path>
		<name>Space Harrier</name>
		<desc>Run… fly… dodge those obstacles, but return fire on wave after wave of attacking aliens. Armed with a really big gun, you have to defend yourself against the alien hordes using your wits to navigate around the screen. But watch out for those end of level bosses!</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Space Harrier-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Space Harrier-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Space Harrier-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Robin Hood, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Robin Hood</name>
		<desc>In Robin Hood you must perform many heroic deeds to change the public impression of you from "villain" to "hero." To he ultimate aim is to retake your castle, which is captured in the intro sequence. This involves bringing together your band of merry men, and killing the Sheriff and his guards. There are around 6 extra items you can find in the game, most of which aren't essential but make the game a lot easier. The whole interface is similar to Populous: you don't direct Robin directly but with icons which are placed around the screen.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Adventures of Robin Hood, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Adventures of Robin Hood, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Adventures of Robin Hood, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hotshot.zip</path>
		<name>Hotshot</name>
		<desc>A simple two-player game released to much marketing fanfare, Hotshot places you and another player (either another person or an AI robot) in an arena split down the middle into two save for a hole about half the screen's height for the ball to travel through, with a series of bricks on each side to destroy.

The aim of the game is to destroy your own bricks before your opponent can destroy his. This is achieved by catching the small by pointing your suction device at it and holding fire, and then releasing in the needed by letting go of the button. This is easier said than done, as the ball neither moves in a straight line or according to the natural rules of.gravity.

Should either player be hit with the ball and not catch it properly, they will be knocked down and possession of the ball is passed to the other player.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Hotshot-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Hotshot-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hotshot-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxwell Technology</developer>
		<publisher>Prism Leisure</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Obliterator.zip</path>
		<name>Obliterator</name>
		<desc>You play Drak, the last of the Obliterators (genetically enhanced machines bio engineered for otherwise impossible missions.) Your mission is to save the Federation from an alien spacecraft. 

Obliterator is an arcade style platform action game. The game screens are static (instead of scrolling, though you can optionally turn on scrolling transitions between screens.) and can be maze like at times with many locations to search. Armed with a variety of weapons, you have to board the alien spacecraft, disable its weapons, plasma drives and shields, then escape.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Obliterator-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Obliterator-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Obliterator-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Black Tiger.zip</path>
		<name>Black Tiger</name>
		<desc>You are a barbarian who must slay three dragons that descended from the skies and plunged the kingdom into darkness. You must go through several areas, destroying monsters that get in your way. Along the way, you will come across old men, which when rescued, will give you a range of items that include extra time, more vitality, or more coins, or they might sell you items, including armor upgrades, weapons, keys for treasure chests, anti-poisoning potions. But, as always, you need to collect coins, which can be obtained by destroying certain monsters or breaking a series of pots.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Black Tiger-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Black Tiger-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Black Tiger-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Black Tiger-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Twins.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Twins</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Mega Twins-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Mega Twins-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mega Twins-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mega Twins-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Twilight</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire and Forget II - The Death Convoy.zip</path>
		<name>Fire and Forget II - The Death Convoy</name>
		<desc>Part two in the Fire and Forget series, best described as Crazy Cars (also by Titus) with weapons in a futuristic setting. This game combines the genres action and driving.

In each of the five levels you need to blow your way to the front of the death convoy and shot down the leader of a group of terrorists, who plans to blow up a city. Your machine of destruction is a car with the ability to fly.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Fire and Forget II - The Death Convoy-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Fire and Forget II - The Death Convoy-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Fire and Forget II - The Death Convoy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Fire and Forget II - The Death Convoy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guardian Angel.zip</path>
		<name>Guardian Angel</name>
		<desc>In the future NYC has become inhospitable and depraved, with thugs lining every street waiting to pounce on ordinary civilians. Thankfully Freddy Hardest is on hand to face up to the baseball bats and knives, in a side-scrolling beat 'em up game.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Guardian Angel-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Guardian Angel-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Iron Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Briga de rua</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Growth.zip</path>
		<name>Growth</name>
		<desc>Growth is an arcade game loosely extending the Arkanoid principle, shifting the focus from the classic ball and bat schema more on the shooting bat extra weapon of Arkanoid and only adding he ball as bonus.nnnnThe player controls the bat and can not only move it at the bottom of the screen, but also around the screen borders, so you can move it to the left, right and top of the screen as well. The bat have shooting abilities by default, which is badly required, as the eye in the center of the screen is constantly popping up new stones to the playfield. A life is lost if the growing stone formation is reaching any border. The goal in most levels is to simply destroy the eye in the center of the screen, which can be achieved by shooting through the stones until the eye itself can be hit while controlling the expansion of the stones.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Growth-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pulse</developer>
		<publisher>Eclipse</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exolon.zip</path>
		<name>Exolon</name>
		<desc>This action game combines shoot 'em up and platform elements, as you control a flying man who can gain an exoskeletal suit for extra protection (hence the name). Your task is to progress from left to right in each level, either along the ground or by using the arrangement of platforms. Most of the baddies can be avoided rather than shot, and this is often easier, especially as you can duck or jump to avoid them. As well as a standard gun (activated by tapping fire) you also have a limited number of missiles to take out installations (activated by holding down fire, which makes autofire facilities useless). The scrolling is flick-screen, perhaps as the game was designed for the C64, and the Amiga version was identical to the ST's.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Exolon-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Exolon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Exolon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Drakkhen.zip</path>
		<name>Drakkhen</name>
		<desc>ANHAK DRAKKHEN AGHNAHIR HURTHD!

The prophecy has been fulfilled. The world shall be ruled by the dragons. On an island far away, their lords prepare for the conquest of the lands. There is only one hope for mankind. The emperor sends out four heroes -- warriors and magicians -- to solve the puzzle of tears and prevent the invasion of the Drakkhen.

Drakkhen is a role-playing game with several ingenious features for its time. The eye-catcher is a mix of fast 3D landscapes and 2D interiors. The player's party will travel overland on a flat terrain made up of vectors, on which 2D objects are zoomed (The same type of engine was later used in Eternam). The player will encounter monsters and fight them in real-time combat, and discover the palaces of the dragon lords. Indoors, the player has to find a way through the maze of chambers, solving puzzles and defeating the minions of the Drakkhen. Party members are depicted in four status windows on the left side of the screen, thus allowing to see their current status and equipment at once.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Drakkhen-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Drakkhen-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Drakkhen-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Drakkhen-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./President is Missing, The.zip</path>
		<name>The President is Missing</name>
		<desc>The President of the USA and other heads of state were kidnapped! It's up to you as a special investigator to find them. In this text-based adventure mystery you must wade through piles of information, and send agents into the field to investigate suspects, all in the hopes of catching the culprits and saving the world leaders.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/President is Missing, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/President is Missing, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/President is Missing, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Cosmi Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back.zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back</name>
		<desc>The arcade game from Atari Games based on the second Star Wars movie features four action sequences inspired by the film. The graphical style is similar to the first Star Wars game, using vector graphics with a first-person perspective.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nigel Mansell's World Championship.zip</path>
		<name>Nigel Mansell's World Championship</name>
		<desc>Timing smiled on Gremlin with this licensed Formula 1 simulation, as Nigel's long quest for a championship had finally come good. The game was pitched somewhere in between a full-blown simulation like F1 GP and action games like Continental Circus. Only 12 cars were in each race, which could last from between 3 and 20 laps.

Before each race you can customize wing downforce, gear ratio, tyre selection and fuel load choices – pitstops are a standard feature of the longer races. The 16-bit versions include a unique 'Improve With Mansell' mode, in which a digitized version of Nigel's head appears in the top corner of the screen, offering instructions and praise.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Nigel Mansell's World Championship-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Nigel Mansell's World Championship-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nigel Mansell's World Championship-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Laser Squad.zip</path>
		<name>Laser Squad</name>
		<desc>Laser Squad is by the same designer as Microprose's classic X-Com: UFO Defense. It brings to the table an immersive gameplay environment as well as many innovative ideas that weren't available in any other game of the time.

In Laser Squad you control a group of "marine"-like soldiers (and the occasional cyborg). Before taking them into battle, you must buy them weapons and armour with a predetermined amount of credits, taking into account the individual abilities of your squad. Unlike X-COM, the soldiers do not gain experience over time.

There are 3 missions in turn - in The Assassins you must face down Sterner Regnix and his guards, Moonbase assault challenges you to destroy the OmniCorp database, and Rescue From the Mines eschews violence in favour of a rescue mission. These are viewed from above and progress in turns. Laser Squad also features a 2-player "hotseat"-type gaming option.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Target Games Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Blade Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klax.zip</path>
		<name>Klax</name>
		<desc>An action/puzzle game, the object is to catch assorted color falling tiles and create rows, columns, or diagonals of a single color. Each level requires a different pattern to be made, and the tiles fall faster, more at a time, and in an increasing number of colors as the game progresses.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari Info</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xenon.zip</path>
		<name>Xenon</name>
		<desc>Xenon is the obscure and mysterious predecessor to the much better known Xenon 2: Megablast. The game is actually nothing like its sequel, with completely different control scheme and gameplay. The plot overlaps however, with the Xenites making their first attempt to control the galaxy.

Xenon is essentially an overhead shooter, where the player controls the ship and moves around the screen. However, the difference between Xenon and its sequel is that here the player actually controls the movement of the playfield (up or down) by simply moving the ship in the direction of choice. To do this in the sequel, players need to slam your ship against the bottom of the screen and pull back on the stick in order to reverse-scroll the playfield.

It also features a 3D playfield (some enemies, for example, will be mounted on hills of sort, where players can't shoot them). To combat these the player can transform its tank into a plane. The game then switches to the more familiar gameplay style as seen in other vertically scrolling shooters. The plane has to transform back into a tank again to combat most ground units.

In Xenon, upgrades are taken from destroyed enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Bitmap Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Championship Boxing Manager.zip</path>
		<name>World Championship Boxing Manager</name>
		<desc>Manage a stable of 3 wannabe heavyweight world champions in this unusual twist of the standard football management style. The option are selected through an icon-based system, representing your office.

Training your fighters involves deciding which areas they should work on, considering their strengths and weaknesses and any damage inflicted in previous fights, and those of their next opponent. 

There are 97 of these in the game, so reaching the top of the rankings will take 15-20 fights, just like real life. Choosing a beatable opponent, but one who can get your fight as high up the Friday Night bill as possible, negotiating the best financial deal, and a mutually agreeable dare, are the main considerations.

Two different governing bodies are included in the game, each with subtly different rules, and a fight in one set of rules won’t be viewed quite as significantly by the other.

The matches are presented from the commentary box, with the 2 expert analysts exchanging textual descriptions of the key punches, and who is dong the best (a clue to how any judges’ decision would go). Before and during the fights you can instruct your man as to what tactics to adopt.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Goliath Games</developer>
		<publisher>Goliath Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Where Time Stood Still.zip</path>
		<name>Where Time Stood Still</name>
		<desc>While flying three members of the same family, your planes crash-lands in an area where it soon becomes clear that time has stood still - dinosaurs still roam the area, and the humans are primitive and carnivorous. Your task is to guide them to safety through the complex isometrically viewed world (using the same basic game engine as Denton Designs' Great Escape license).

Hazards to be faced include the aforementioned dinosaurs and cavemen, as well as sea monsters, precarious mountainous ledges and dilapidated bridges. Objects including weapons and first aid kits can be collected. Each character has his own distinct behaviors - one becomes hungry easily, while another is only really competent while his fiancé survives. Although the ultimate aim is to save all four characters, you can continue while at least one is alive.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TV Sports Football.zip</path>
		<name>TV Sports Football</name>
		<desc>Before Electronic Arts sought to imitate television coverage of sports with their EA Sports titles, Cinemaware had the same idea, initially applying it to (American) Football. Cutscenes follow dramatic moments in the match, and each match is preceded by a TV-style introduction. The game is primarily action-based, although you also choose your plays before executing them. You then bring the passes and runs to life on the pitch itself. You can play single matches or full leagues, with any of the NFL teams of the time.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cinemaware</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Futebol americano</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gazza's Super Soccer.zip</path>
		<name>Gazza's Super Soccer</name>
		<desc>This was the first of the two football games licensed around Paul Gascoigne, then the most expensive player in British football history. The game is viewed top down, and can be set to either move left-right or top-bottom.

League and cup tournaments are included, as are single matches and set-piece practice sections (you have full control of these). The gameplay involves a number of advanced moves, and includes a gauge to control the exact dimensions of a kick (height and curl as well as strength), if you can use it quickly enough. Unusually, you have control over the goalkeeper, so can only blame yourself when you concede a goal. The players each have their own skills and strengths, and these develop as the game goes on – if you play well, your players become better, and more capable of facing better opposition.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Empire Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Cricket.zip</path>
		<name>Championship Cricket</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Championship Cricket-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Crysys</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Revenge II - Revenge of the Mutant Camels II.zip</path>
		<name>Revenge II - Revenge of the Mutant Camels II</name>
		<desc>Jeff Minter's third camel-themed game (after Attack and Revenge) is again a horizontally scrolling shoot 'em up, taking place over 100 levels. 6,000 years ago, mankind fought the forces of Zzyax, using mutated forms of common animals. Now, the Zzyaxians are back, and the 90-foot camels must defend a planet no longer accustomed to warfare.</desc>
		<developer>Llamasoft Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sinbad and the Throne of the Falcon.zip</path>
		<name>Sinbad and the Throne of the Falcon</name>
		<desc>Take to the high seas as Sinbad the sailor. You have been asked for help by the Princess to defeat the Black Prince and his minions from hell. You will fight pirates and genies, find romance and heartbreak, comedy and tragedy.

Sinbad is a more action-oriented game than other adventure/strategy releases from Cinemaware. Featuring loads of arcade sequences and limited decision making.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cinemaware</developer>
		<publisher>Cinemaware</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./War in Middle Earth.zip</path>
		<name>War in Middle Earth</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Synergistic Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chip's Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Chips Challenge</name>
		<desc>Nerdy Chip desperately wants to join the "Bit Busters" computer club, led by Melinda the Mental Marvel.  However, before she'll let him in, he must prove his intelligence by passing the initiation test.  149 increasingly difficult levels, including a few hidden ones, await Chip in this tile-based puzzle game.  Use tools such as keys, and special shoes to bypass obstacles.  Manipulate switches to and use dirt blocks to build bridges across waterways.  Avoid enemy creatures, grab all the computer chips in the level, and hurry to the exit: On top of everything else, there's a time limit!</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thrust.zip</path>
		<name>Thrust</name>
		<desc>Thrust took a unique game style by bringing realistic physics and inertia-based movement into arcade games, directly influencing titles like Oids, not to mention the same author's Exile from Audiogenic. The action is viewed from the side, with the graphics drawn in vectors, in keeping with the mathematical nature of everything that unfolds.

As a Resistance fighter, the player must fly into enemy lines in order to steal Klystron Pods to power more advanced starships, using your tractor beam to take them. A network of mounted guns are aiming to shoot the player down – these can be disabled by shooting their power source, but eventually this will explode, forcing the player to flee. Some of the later levels feature reverse gravity, which is where things really get difficult.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebird</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Red Heat.zip</path>
		<name>Red Heat</name>
		<desc>Red Heat is based on the Walter Hill film of the same name, starring Arnold Schwarzenegger and James Belushi. You take control of Soviet detective Ivan Danko (played by Schwarzenegger), who travels to Chicago in pursuit of the fearsome Georgian drug lord Victor Rosta. 

The game is essentially a side-scrolling beat'em up in the vein of Vigilante. As Danko, you proceed across four levels which follow the movie's original setting, where you are constantly attacked by members of the Cleanheads, a group of drug-dealers who are in business with Victor Rosta. To eliminate hostiles you can either punch them (slow but long-ranged) or head-butt them (close-ranged but faster). The only defensive move available is crouching, so as to avoid being hit - there is no jumping or any other evasive tactics. Occasionally, you can get hold of a handgun and fire six shots at the villains. Other items you can pick up will boost your health, make you temporarily invulnerable or give you access to bonus levels.

One peculiarity of Red Heat is its widescreen-like game area, and the fact that all characters are drawn from the waist up. This may find partial explanation in the first level, set in a Russian sauna where, as in the original movie scene, all characters are not wearing clothes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Special FX Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Streets.zip</path>
		<name>Wild Streets</name>
		<desc>New-York, Year 1998. The once most prestigious city in the world, has now become a fighting zone. Half of the city is left in ruins, and it is in that part of town that the marginals and gangs are living, hunted by every law enforcement agencies. The other half of the city consists of fancy mansions, in some of which the most important drug barons reside. Unfortunately, they are the ones who run the city using the enormous profits they make from dealing drugs and weapons. They now have succeeded in endangering the country's economy.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Briga de rua</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advanced Rugby Simulator.zip</path>
		<name>Advanced Rugby Simulator</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Balance of Power - The 1990 Edition.zip</path>
		<name>Balance of Power - The 1990 Edition</name>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incredible Technologies Inc</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Return of the Jedi.zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars - Return of the Jedi</name>
		<desc>The arcade game from Atari based on the third Star Wars movie features three action sequences inspired by the film.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puzznic.zip</path>
		<name>Puzznic</name>
		<desc>The challenge in each level of Puzznic is to maneuvre a selection of blocks into place so as to clear them all, by making them make contact with blocks of the same design. You control a cross-hair, which can move a block left or right, which can cause it to fall if there is no block under the space it would occupy.

There are many complications in terms of solving the levels. Moving platforms meaning that you need to move a block at a particular time, or in particular order, to prevent them being blockaded. In some situations there are an odd number of a certain type of block - solving these requires positioning two of the blocks one space apart, such that a move will result in a piece making contact with 2 others, and immediately removing all 3. You will also encounter blocks positioned on platforms suspended in space and gaps in level arrangements meaning that a certain number of blocks must be in place to make a certain move possible (by forming a stack, for example)

The game structure is slightly unusual, as after you complete each batch of four levels you get a choice of 2 sets of levels - you are progressing through an expanding matrix of levels, which means there are 2 sets on level 2, 3 on level 3, 4 on level 4, and so on. This means that there are a total of 220 screens in the game. Each screen is played against a time limit, and losing a level (either by running out of time, or by making a poor move and leaving an impossible position) loses one of your 3 lives.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oriental Games.zip</path>
		<name>Oriental Games</name>
		<desc>The Oriental Games offer skilled martial artists the chance to prove themselves in Kung Fu, Kendo and the relatively brutal Kyo-Kus-Hin-Kai., using “courage, skill and flare” (sic) according to the packaging. It makes for a series of one-on-one fights viewed from the side.

Kendo involves using a stick as your weapon, whereas Kung Fu various punches and kicks and Kyo-Kus-Hin-Kai involves head butts and flying attacks. You can jump over opponents; a quick tap of the fire button turns you around. You have an energy bar with 5 blocks of gradually decreasing colours, which drops when you are hit and increases as you pass time without being hit. Impressive moves earn you bonus Merit Awards.

On the 16-bit versions, there are 3 skill levels (Novice, Professional and Master), digitised sound, and an editor to set up joystick moves. The 8-bit versions lack these niceties, but include an extra discipline, Sumo; these are played in sequence rather than by choice.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micro Style</developer>
		<publisher>Micro Style</publisher>
		<genre>Luta</genre>
		<players>8+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beastlord.zip</path>
		<name>Beast Lord</name>
		<desc>Beastlord is an action game with puzzle-solving elements. The Lord of Darkness managed to trick the three guardians of the world (a unicorn, a hawk and a beam of light) into imprisonment and now overruns everything with his orc hordes. The player takes the role of a young man, who is called the Beastlord because he can interact with animals, and has to explore three levels with the goal to free the guardians. The levels are side-scrolling in nature, but there are many branches to map out.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayne J. Smithson Design</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainment Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Day of the Viper.zip</path>
		<name>Day of the Viper</name>
		<desc>The Sun League has been trying to fight back against the corrupted and oppressive Gar computer for many years. Now they have attacked a defense base. The only hope is for a Viper V droid to be sent in under your control to reactivate the planet's defenses.

To do this, you must find floppy disks that are everywhere in the station to reboot that evil computer! To complete this task, you must fight 33 types of little robots who attack you. The action is viewed in first-person 3D, with directional arrows on screen for movement and rotation.

There are 25 levels, each of which is automatically mapped as you explore it. Use turbolifts to get to them. Each object is managed by the game, and a notepad feature is provided to allow you to keep track of vital information.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Accolade</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hill Street Blues.zip</path>
		<name>Hill Street Blues</name>
		<desc>Hill Street Blues is a top-down action / strategy mix.

“Let’s be careful out there!”

Based on the ‘80s TV drama series Hill Street Blues, this game puts you in the role of Captain Furillo of the Hill Street police department. Crime rates are soaring in the precinct, and it’s up to your team of nine officers (all well-known from the series and with digitized portraits) to keep the streets safe.

Your officers move on foot or by car on a 2D top-down map of the city, complete with real-time traffic. True to the series, each day starts with a roll call from Sgt. Esterhaus. Once on duty, listen to radio operator A.J. Hill report crimes every few minutes. Deploy officers to the scene, help the victim and call an ambulance or coroner; next, identify and find the suspect. Some criminals may flee, others even shoot at you. Give chase or open fire if necessary. When the bad guy is arrested, a court trial may follow.

Hill Street Blues is controlled entirely with the mouse via a set of icons – that’s everything but intuitive, especially when directing a single officer through the streets. Since there will soon be multiple crimes all over the city, the challenge is to co-ordinate multiple officers simultaneously and keep track of cases and suspects. If your success rate is high enough, you will ultimately be promoted to chief of police.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Storm Master.zip</path>
		<name>Storm Master</name>
		<desc>Eoliae is a remote land where myth meets truth, and where winds shows only the power of gods moving armies from front to front, while diplomacy is still 'hanging' in the air full of crossing winds. The chaos was born as the Great master was murdered, and evil Sharkaan is threatening all of the Eoliae land. You must learn the power of the winds, gain the knowledge for trade and diplomacy, build windmills and strike your enemy where it hurts the most. Only try doing that and stay alive.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silmarils</developer>
		<publisher>Silmarils</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Driller.zip</path>
		<name>Driller</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incentive Software</developer>
		<publisher>Incentive Software</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Outcast.zip</path>
		<name>Outcast</name>
		<desc>Running away from the Hive seems like a good idea - until they catch up with you. Outcasts are not well thought of by the collective Mind. To stay alive now you'll have to defend your few bases as best you can so that the larvae within can hatch and you can start your own Hive. Then you can take on the Mind on your own terms.

Right now, however, with the sky full of Swarmers, Seekers and Seigers the future does not look all that bright. Take up your flight and SURVIVE.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tennis Cup.zip</path>
		<name>Tennis Cup</name>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Loriciel SA</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciel SA</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Tênis</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mach 3.zip</path>
		<name>Mach 3</name>
		<desc>Kill all the enemies, avoid the mines, and travel between distinct worlds to kill the evil mastermind in this behind-the-hero view shooter.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Loriciels</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciels</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Corruption.zip</path>
		<name>Corruption</name>
		<desc>Corruption is one of Magnetic Scrolls interactive fiction games. It is also one of the few 'real world' based games (ie: no elves, magic, etc).

You play a stockbroker on the fast track to riches when suddenly there are attempts on your life and the words 'insider dealings' floating around!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magnetic Scrolls</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hunter Killer.zip</path>
		<name>Hunter Killer</name>
		<desc>Relive the war in the pacific:
Experience the reality of commanding an American World War II combat submarine operating in the south pacific.

Master the controls of your vessel, then embark on a series of missions - from straightforward 'search and destroy' sorties to detailed escort duties modelled on real WWII campaigns.

Eleven different submarines are featured, with fourteen seperate missions to attempt at a range of difficulty levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Solaco Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>16 Blitz</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Killing Cloud, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Killing Cloud</name>
		<desc>Killing Cloud is set in a San Francisco ravaged by an opaque orange death smog layer known as the Killing Cloud. This hovers around the middle of the skyscrapers, creating a claustrophobic low level experience (and a different feel to the many other flight simulations set in the city, such as F/A-18 Interceptor).

In this maelstrom, the Black Angel gang is terrorising the public. The player is a member of the SFPD Police force, charged with bringing them down throughout ten missions. Some are out-and-out action while others are more strategic. You can only survive for 20 minutes in the smog, so time is crucial in these missions.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vektor Grafix</developer>
		<publisher>Image Works</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Treble Champions.zip</path>
		<name>Treble Champions</name>
		<desc>Treble Champions is a football management game. The player can manage a squad, train players, and try to gain the way to the top of the leagues and cups. There are four divisions of 20 teams each and 1,500 (fictional) players with individual attributes are included in the game and purchasable for the manager. Beside the squad skills and injuries, the finances have to be managed for further progress in the game.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Treble Champions-image.png</image>
		<developer>Mr. Micro Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Challenge Software</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte / Futebol</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Carrier Command.zip</path>
		<name>Carrier Command</name>
		<desc>Carrier Command was one of the first real-time strategy games.

You control an advanced cybernetic aircraft carrier complete with fighters, amphibious assault vehicles, laser defenses and a fleet of decoy drones.  Your mission is to build a series of resource, factory, and defensive bases spanning an island chain.  The only problem?  At the other end of the chain is an even more advanced carrier under control of a terrorist organization with the same mission.

As you move around the islands you must decide what facilities to build and where they will best support your advance.  Resource islands provide materials that factory islands can use to build weapons and vehicles to replace your combat losses but both will be quickly overrun if the enemy attacks them while you are not present.  You also have to ensure that your stockpiles of equipment are stored safely until you can find time to launch a resupply drone to bring them to your carrier.

From your carrier, you can take first person control of your attack aircraft and amphibious tanks and use them to assault enemy islands or even the enemy carrier itself if you're lucky enough to find it.  The weapon payloads on your vehicles are completely configurable based on your needs.  An island invasion may require launching a virus bomb that will take over the enemy command systems or just blasting the base with a wire guided surface to surface missile.

Ultimately, you have to find and destroy the enemy carrier but, doing so will require a solid supply infrastructure and a strategy for depriving your opponent of his.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crack Down.zip</path>
		<name>Crackdown</name>
		<desc>Crack Down is a time-limited action game. The two heroes, Ben and Andy, have to get through the levels as quickly as possible placing bombs on X marks scattered around the levels. Although the levels are heavily defended, the player has an array of weaponry including a cannon, machine gun, and superbombs. 

The game may be played as either a one or two-player game.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trailblazer.zip</path>
		<name>Trailblazer</name>
		<desc>An imaginative action game in which you must guide a ball-shaped craft through a succession of levels. These have a patchwork-quilt type display, with holes to avoid, and squares of various colors, which affect the craft's speed, both within its power potential and into warp, as well as a control-reverser and lots of holes. You can jump these holes by pressing fire, although you have a limited number of these for each level, and adjust the speed by pulling the joystick forward or backwards.  You face a time limit on each of the 21 levels, although your time is boosted every time you complete one. A simultaneous 2-player mode is included, similar to the split-screen mode in the Lotus games (by the same authors).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Mr Chip Software</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Foundation's Waste.zip</path>
		<name>Foundation's Waste</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Exocet Software</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guild of Thieves, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Guild of Thieves</name>
		<desc>As a beginner and inducted into the "Guild Of Thieves", you must steal your way to the top - the Guildmaster is there to not only help you, but to make your life a living hell. Worst of it all is you're STILL in the land of Kerovnia.....if something makes it look tough to solve, that's nothing for a puzzle - something else will screw it up more.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magnetic Scrolls</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Italy 1990.zip</path>
		<name>Italy '90</name>
		<desc>World Class Soccer is a soccer (football) game that ties in with the 1990 football World Cup. The game uses a top-down perspective for matches and features the full World Cup structure and all the 24 teams who were involved. Multiple formations and team selections are available before each match. The ball sticks to the feet of the players, who can be tackled either by doing a block tackle, or attempting a slide tackle, which risks giving away a foul. Matches can vary between 4 and 90 minutes, and each player has differing skills and behaviour style depending on his team's relative ability.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tiertex</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Action Service.zip</path>
		<name>Action Service</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sargon III.zip</path>
		<name>Sargon III</name>
		<desc>The Sargon series were the connisseur's chess games at the time. This edition includes variable move times, ranging from 5 seconds to infinity. Moves can be undone and you can swap sides during the game. The search feature displays its calculations as you play, which can be useful to learn from. Special tactical situations, opening move sequences and checkmate practices can be loaded in for learning purposes.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Logotron</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pictionary - The Game of Quick Draw.zip</path>
		<name>Pictionary</name>
		<desc>Based on the board game, the object is guess a word or phrase based on a drawing. There are five categories - Person/Place/Animal, Object, Action, a category of difficult puzzles, and an All Play category. The amount of time to guess an answer can be alte</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oxford Mobius</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Jogo de tabuleiro</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./StarFlight.zip</path>
		<name>Starflight</name>
		<desc>A long time ago, a great empire comprised of Humans, Velox, Thrynn and Elowan ruled the stars. The Empire's currency was an energy source called Endurium. But something happened and this empire is no more. Furthermore, the small colony world named Arth has forgotten this heritage and technology. 1000 years have since passed and the people of Arth have rediscovered archaeological evidence of their empire. Using these discoveries, they create spaceships and form the Interstel corporation to govern the fleet. It's time to take the first steps back into space... but could it be the same enemy that destroyed the Empire still exists?

Starflight is a space exploration game. The player must first form a crew, assign their positions and customize the spaceship before blasting off from spacedock. Once out into space, the standard interface allows access to different crew members and navigation. The entire galaxy is unknown and it's up to the player to travel to distant planets to explore and land on them. Using a top-down interface, a planetary lander will venture out with the task of  finding minerals and biological data to transport back to Starport. These resources can then be used to train crew members and improve the ship. Different alien races control the galaxy and it will be up to the player to engage them diplomatically or engage them in combat. Successful exploration of the galaxy and alien cultures will yield clues and new leads as to the fate of the Empire.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Binary Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom.zip</path>
		<name>Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom</name>
		<desc>The computer versions of Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom are conversions of the Atari arcade game based on the second movie in the series. As Indy you must complete several cycles of the following 3 types of levels:Mine level: Whip your way through a mine in order to free children that are held captive. Use your whip to swing across chasms, climb ladders, ride along conveyor belts and defend yourself against attacks from Thuggee guards, bats, snakes and the fireball-throwing Mola ram. Escape with the mine cart after you've freed all children.
2. Mine cart level: Pick the right route through a network of tracks while riding in a mine cart. Avoid potholes, broken tracks &amp; guards in carts and safely reach the end of the track.
3. Temple level: Make your way to the altar and grab the Sankara stone while Mola Ram, bats and Thuggee guards attack you. Watch out for that lava.
With every cycle the mine &amp; mine cart levels become more complex, the layout of the temple levels is always the same. After several cycles there's a showdown with Mola Ram on the rope bridge.</desc>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paragon Software</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyberball.zip</path>
		<name>Cyberball</name>
		<desc>After American Football players started cheating by using bionic parts, the game was forced to change its rules. By 2022, the game was played not by humans, but two teams of seven robots. To spice things up, the usual pig skin ball was replaced with a 350 pound bomb.

Cyberball brings this fast and furious action to life. Gameplay is essentially the same as the real sport, although the 'downs' are replaced by the bomb's heat gradually increasing towards 'critical'. After this it will explode and possession will be swapped. This is prevented when you cross the 50-yard line, lose possession or score a touchdown, in which cases it resets to 'cool'. Field goals and punts are not featured - the only kick is the initial kick-off you receive.

Control passes from the quarterback (thrower) to the intended catcher as soon as a pass is released. The two-player game is co-operative - on offense one player passes and the other receives</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warlock's Quest.zip</path>
		<name>Warlock's Quest</name>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>ERE</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./James Pond II - Codename RoboCod.zip</path>
		<name>James Pond II - Codename Robocod</name>
		<desc>In his second adventure James Pond must retrieve the toys Dr Maybe has stolen. Pond has been armed with an Inspector Gadget-style stretch device, which he can use to view higher areas or claw onto ceilings so as to slide across them.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vectordean</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon.zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>Set in a post-apocalyptic New York, Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers trained in the fighting style of Sou-Setsu-Ken. Together, they manage a small martial arts training school, teaching their students in self-defense. One day, Billy's girlfriend, Marian, is kidnapped off the street by the &amp;quot;Black Warriors&amp;quot;, a savage street gang led by a man named Willy. The Black Warriors demand the Lee brothers disclose their martial arts secrets in exchange for Marian's freedom. The Lee brothers set out on a rescue mission to crush the Black Warriors and save Marian.

Using whatever techniques they have at their disposal, from the basic punches and kicks to the invulnerable elbow strike, as well any weapon that comes into their hands, the Lee brothers must pursue the gang through the city slum, industrial area and the forest before reaching their hideout to confront the big boss, Willy.

The NES version of this game also has an additional VS. fighting mode for one or two players. Players choose from a field of six different characters (Billy and 5 of the enemy characters) and enter into a one-on-one fighting match. Players have to punch, kick, jumpkick, and even use a weapon against their opponents until someone's health bar is fully drained. The winner is the last one standing.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Briga de rua</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sundog - Frozen Legacy.zip</path>
		<name>Sundog - Frozen Legacy</name>
		<desc>You just inherited a one-man star freighter - the SunDog - from an uncle who died under mysterious circumstances. You also inherited the contract he signed to aid in the building of a colony for a religious group. You have three tasks to perform: find the location of the colony; find, buy, and deliver goods needed for its construction; and locate the cryogenically-frozen colonists needed to populate the colony.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FTL Games</developer>
		<publisher>FTL Games</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Ninja Rabbits.zip</path>
		<name>International Ninja Rabbits</name>
		<desc>Having saved the day by destroying a chemical plant in Ninja Rabbits, Bugs must now travel the world and destroy several more chemical plants to save the environment from pollution. To get to each plant our hero must walk from left to right on a scrolling side view game. Bugs doesn't just have to travel above ground but has the option in various places to go underground as well.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/International Ninja Rabbits-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/International Ninja Rabbits-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/International Ninja Rabbits-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Flair Software</developer>
		<publisher>Micro Value</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RoboCop.zip</path>
		<name>Robocop</name>
		<desc>Patrolman Alex Murphy was killed on the streets of Detroit. The major corporation there, Omni Consumer Products (OCP) saw an opportunity to sell a new kind of law enforcement officer to the troubled city. They took what was left of Murphy, encased it in titanium armor, wiped his memory and created RoboCop. Now it's up to RoboCop to clean the streets of Detroit and eliminate the one responsible for his murder, Clarence Boddicker. But it looks like Clarence might not be the kingpin of this town...

Based on the 1987 movie of the same name, RoboCop allows the player to control RoboCop. The majority of the game is a side scroller. RoboCop can punch unarmed citizens and shoot armed citizens. He can move left, right and duck but can not jump. Different weapons can be picked up from enemies, and power-ups to restore health and/or energy. Following levels, RoboCop will have to match a criminal's face to the proper mugshot and engage in a first-person shooting bonus round.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/RoboCop-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/RoboCop-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/RoboCop-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/RoboCop-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trivial Pursuit - A New Beginning.zip</path>
		<name>Trivial Persuit - A new Beginning</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Trivial Pursuit - A New Beginning-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Trivial Pursuit - A New Beginning-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Trivial Pursuit - A New Beginning-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oxford Mobius</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Jogo de tabuleiro</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Populous - The Promised Lands.zip</path>
		<name>Populous - The Promised Lands</name>
		<desc>This Data Disk for Populous adds five new landscape types: Wild West, Silly Land, Block Land, Révolution Française and Bit Plains. The types can be used to create new maps in Paint Map mode and the disk also has 500 new maps for Conquest mode.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Populous - The Promised Lands-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Populous - The Promised Lands-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Populous - The Promised Lands-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Overlander.zip</path>
		<name>Overlander</name>
		<desc>Overlander sees Elite attempt a Roadblasters style driving game with shooting overtones, with the action viewed from behind your armour-plated well-armed car. It all takes place in a post-apocalyptic universe in which a lot of money can be earned by transporting goods form place to place, but the large gangs of Overlanders who already do this are keen to stop you.

Two missions are on offer at a time, one tougher but more lucrative than the other, with half the money paid upfront and the other half on successful completion. Before setting off, you can buy upgrades such as turbo chargers, armour and enhanced weapons, each of which has a limited lifespan. Attacks from other vehicles can come either from guns or attempting ramming, and the roads are poorly-maintained and hazardous, so be careful, or better yet be violent first.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Overlander-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Overlander-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Overlander-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Overlander-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gemini Wing.zip</path>
		<name>Gemini Wings</name>
		<desc>Humans and aliens are living in harmony in the future, until a tabloid journalist stirs up hatred towards aliens. They respond by invading the planet, and it's down to you to clear up a situation scarily similar to reality in this arcade conversion.

Gemini Wing is a vertically-scrolling shoot 'em up, which is distinguished by its unusual power-up system. Instead of gaining occasional tokens which lead to lasting weaponry improvements, occasional flurries of tokens are released to ensure a quick burst of improved fire. The organic backgrounds are detailed, and have many sections which fire at you.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Gemini Wing-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Gemini Wing-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Gemini Wing-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Gemini Wing-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-19 Stealth Fighter.zip</path>
		<name>F-19 Stealth Fighter</name>
		<desc>Rule the night! Take the pride of American Stealth technology and take on the best the Warsaw pact technology can offer! Dodge between radars, sneak under enemy fighters, and take out your primary objectives and secondary objectives with your limited weapons onboard, then make your way home. Can you survive all the way to general and win the Congressional Medal of Honor?

F-19 Stealth Fighter was based around Sid Meier's closest estimate of the stealth fighter based on the data available at the time. You get full 3D graphics, 3D enemies, random objectives and enemy dispositions (so each mission will be different), dynamic radar effectiveness that depends on your position and radar cross section, enemies that search you out if you do "tickle" their defenses, even civilian aircrafts in the air, and ability to play in cold war, moderate war, or all-out war, with very different rules of engagement.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/F-19 Stealth Fighter-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/F-19 Stealth Fighter-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trinity.zip</path>
		<name>Trinity</name>
		<desc>(From Infocom Home Page fan site)

You're neither an adventurer nor a professional trill-seeker. You're simply an American tourist in London, enjoying a relaxing stroll through the famous Kensington Gardens. When World War III starts and the city is vaporized moments after the story begins, you have no hope of survival. Unless you enter another time, another place, another dimension. Escaping the destruction of London is not the end of your problems, but rather the beginning of new, more bizarre riddles. You'll find yourself in an exotic world teeming with giant fly traps, strange creatures, and other inconveniences. Time and space will behave with their own intricate and mischievous logic. You'll visit fantastic places and acquire curious objects as you seek to discover the logic behind your newfound universe. And if you can figure out the patter of events, you'll wind up in the New Mexico desert, minutes before the culmination of the greatest scientific experiment of all time: the world's first atomic explosion, code-named Trinity.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Trinity-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Trinity-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Trinity-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infocom</developer>
		<publisher>Infocom</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hound of Shadow, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Hound of Shadow</name>
		<desc>A text adventure game set in HP Lovecraft themes in 1920's.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Hound of Shadow, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Hound of Shadow, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Hound of Shadow, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eldritch Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GFL Championship Football.zip</path>
		<name>GFL Championship Football</name>
		<desc>This must be one of the earliest team sport games to use a first-person view – the packaging mocks the Xs and Os used to represent players in contemporary Gridiron games. What you see is what the player sees – control and viewpoint passes from the kicker to the receiver on a punt or kickoff, and the quarterback to the running back or receiver on a pass or kick. Releasing passes involves rotating the controls to select the pass direction. To take the ball, aim the visible hands in the centre of the screen.

There are 28 teams split into four divisions; their names are fictional (including the Seagulls, Mustangs and Geronimos), and each is rated out of 3 on 8 areas of skill. Matches last for 4 quarters of either 4 or 7 minutes' in-play time. Menus to select plays or teams involve using diagonal movements for selection. 

Standard Gridiron rules apply – gain 10 yards in 4 attempts (downs) without fumbling or having a pass intercepted; kick a punt or field goal if you are about to fail at this.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/GFL Championship Football-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/GFL Championship Football-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/GFL Championship Football-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gamestar</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rally Cross Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Rally Cross Challenge</name>
		<desc>Rallycross racing was once popular on the BBC, featuring super-modified cars racing against each other on tracks combining tarmac and gravel sections. Rally Cross Challenge sees Anco bring it to life in top-view Super Sprint style.

There are six different circuits, and four cars in the game - 16-bit users with a Microdeal joystick adapter can have all four of these controlled by human players, other users are limited to 2-player. Computer cars have varying personalities and abilities. You must finish in the top 3 to move on to the next race.

The opportunity to upgrade your car comes after each race, with the points you earn from race results (4,2,1 for the top 3). There are six categories of upgrades - turbo, steering, traction, aerodynamics, repair time and brakes.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Rally Cross Challenge-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Rally Cross Challenge-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rally Cross Challenge-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Ultra Graphix</developer>
		<publisher>Anco</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chuckie Egg II.zip</path>
		<name>Chuckie Egg II</name>
		<desc>Chuckie Egg II is a sequel to platformer game Chuckie Egg, but is very different from the original game.  Whereas the original game features eight levels of one screen each, this features many more screens arranged into a maze for you to explore.

In the game, Hen House Harry must build a giant chocolate egg, with the ingredients (cocoa, milk and sugar), that are found in the factory.  Eight of each must be included.  Also, the eight parts of a toy kit must be found, to place inside the egg.

In order to get all the items you must find your way around the factory, avoiding many types of enemy, and solving puzzles using various items that you can carry.  There are a number of ways to get around the factory, including the platforms of the original, but also ropes and pipes, among other things.

Despite the drastic changes from the original, the game still retains the sound effects from the original.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Chuckie Egg II-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Chuckie Egg II-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Chuckie Egg II-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Pick &amp; Choose</developer>
		<publisher>A&amp;J Software</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Operation Stealth.zip</path>
		<name>Operation Stealth</name>
		<desc>The Stealth Affair is a graphic adventure game with a point-and-click interface. The player controls the famous secret agent James Bond (John Glames in the European version), whose task is to travel to South America in order to locate and retrieve a newly designed F-19 stealth plane, which was stolen from the Naval Air Station in Miramar, California.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Operation Stealth-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Operation Stealth-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Operation Stealth-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Operation Stealth-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delphine Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Delphine Software International</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heroes of the Lance.zip</path>
		<name>Heroes of the Lance</name>
		<desc>Based on the later parts of the Dragonlance book Dragons of Autumn Twilight, the heroes descend into a ruined city in search of the disks of Mishakal.

The gameplay consists of horizontal fighting with a maze like map using doors to change the view.  The party consists of the 8 Heroes of the Lance, using one at a time and the player can switch between them at any time.  Each character has different types of attacks and spells making them more suited to fighting different enemies as well as acting as lives.

One of the AD&amp;D games that takes a break from the usual RPG style.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Heroes of the Lance-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Heroes of the Lance-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Heroes of the Lance-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Heroes of the Lance-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
		<publisher>Strategic Simulations</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quink.zip</path>
		<name>Quink</name>
		<desc>Quink is a puzzle game for one or two players. In each round of the game, eight names, places, or objects will appear on the screen that will be associated in some way. Out of the eight items, two to six will not be related to the others. The player needs to identify which item(s) are loners and remove them from the list in the given time limit. For each wrong guess the player will lose a life; if three lives are lost, the game ends. Points are awarded for correctly identifying loners; each round contains a goal score, so even if the player completes a round without losing all three lives the goal still needs to be met to proceed onto the next round.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Quink-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Quink-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ron Dubren and Associates</developer>
		<publisher>Thunder Mountain</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Player Manager.zip</path>
		<name>Player Manager</name>
		<desc>You can become the Player-Manager of a third division football team in this innovative action-strategy hybrid. The game features over 1000 fictional individual players to buy and sell, each with 8 different physical and mental skills rated, and you can choose which position to play these in. Four tactical systems are provided, but you can design your own and put it to the test in various situations using a raytrace system. Training sessions are presented visually, allowing you to pinpoint the exact ability and potential of a player.

The playing side of the game uses the Kick Off game engine. After a few seasons your player's ability fades and you eventually have to retire form playing and concentrate on management. You can however save your team and import it into Kick Off 2</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Player Manager-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Player Manager-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anco</developer>
		<publisher>Anco</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rody et Mastico III.zip</path>
		<name>Rody et Mastico III</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Rody et Mastico III-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rody et Mastico III-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<publisher>Lankhor</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goofy's Railway Express.zip</path>
		<name>Goofy's Railway Express</name>
		<desc>Goofy's Railway Express, known as Dingo Et Le Train Express in French, Goofy Und Der Phantastiche Schnellzug in German and Il Rapido Di Pippo in Italian, is a educational game, was released for Atari ST, Commodore 64 and DOS in 1989 in North America, Developed by Disney Software and Published by WestWood Associates, this game starred by Goofy and Mickey who traveling a Train in the other journey.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Goofy's Railway Express-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Goofy's Railway Express-marquee.png</marquee>
		<developer>Westwood</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Software</publisher>
		<genre>Educacional</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wanted.zip</path>
		<name>Wanted</name>
		<desc>Wanted is a vertically scrolling shooter with a Western theme, similar to Gunsmoke. The player takes the role of a bounty hunter who has to bring four desperadoes to justice. They can be tackled in any order and if all are defeated, a fifth level emerges. The gameplay offers no surprises: shooting masses of enemies until reaching the end of the level. The player can shoot barrels to receive extras, e.g. boots for extra speed or a rifle for a better range. Dynamite destroys every enemy on the screen.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Wanted-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Wanted-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Wanted-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<developer>Decroix - Garofalo</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elf.zip</path>
		<name>Elf</name>
		<desc>Elf is a platform game which almost crosses into the adventure genre.  You play an elf who is out to destroy Necrilous the Not-Very-Nice. It's resonably non-linear areas in that you can go back and forth between areas.

You collect items during play and get access to different spells and attacks.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Elf-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Elf-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Elf-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Elf-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nirvana Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Cat Starring in Beverly Hills Cats.zip</path>
		<name>Top Cat Starring In Beverly Hills Cats</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Top Cat Starring in Beverly Hills Cats-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Top Cat Starring in Beverly Hills Cats-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Twilight</developer>
		<publisher>HiTech Software</publisher>
		<genre>Ação / Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghouls 'n' Ghosts.zip</path>
		<name>Ghouls 'n' Ghosts</name>
		<desc>3 years ago (in Ghosts 'N' Goblins), Arthur the brave knight saved Princess PrinPrin from the Dark Prince, Lucifer, and drove his evil forces back into the Underworld. Now, something sinister is again stirring...monsters had returned to attacking the king</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Ghouls 'n' Ghosts-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Ghouls 'n' Ghosts-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ghouls 'n' Ghosts-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./10th Frame.zip</path>
		<name>10th Frame</name>
		<desc>Leader Board authors Bruce and Roger Carver tried their hand at tenpin bowling, in one of the game's earliest recreations. The process of bowling the ball involves timing a succession of clicks to set the right angle, speed and curve, similarly to Leaderboard's system. Three skill levels are provided - Kids level sets the speed and hook automatically, while Amateur has more margin for error with hook/slice than professional. The game is played from a plan view, with four other (empty) lanes visible. Single matches or a league structure can be played.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/10th Frame-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/10th Frame-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/10th Frame-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Access Games</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Apprentice.zip</path>
		<name>Apprentice</name>
		<desc>If you can defeat the dragon Fumo, your status as a magician will be ensured. Many have tried to rid the world of his evil, but none have been strong enough.

Gameplay scrolls sideways and is platform based, with a very cutesy and consolesque look, and 17 levels, each containing an extra hidden section. Each level has its own elemental setting, taking in the fires of Hell and the clouds and light of Heaven. The levels are full of boxes, which can be used as weapons by kicking them at enemies. 

As you go you can also collect money, which can be spent in shops to buy useful extras. Many collectibles and other items exist, such as leaves (which change the effects of gravity, allowing you to jump higher and stay hanging in the air for longer), extra lives, fruit for bonus points, and balloons allowing a degree of vertical movement.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Apprentice-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Apprentice-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Apprentice-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Apprentice-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elite.zip</path>
		<name>Elite</name>
		<desc>Elite is a free-form space trading and combat simulation, commonly considered the progenitor of this sub-genre. The player initially controls a character referred to as &amp;quot;Commander Jameson&amp;quot;, starting at Lave Station with 100 credits and a lightly armed trading ship called Cobra Mark III. Most of the game consists of traveling to various star systems, trading with their inhabitants, gaining money and reputation. Money can also be gained by other means beside trading; these include undertaking military missions, bounty hunting, asteroid mining, and even piracy. As the player character earns money, he becomes able to upgrade his ships with enhancements such as better weapons, shields, increased cargo capacity, an automated docking system, etc.

The game utilizes pseudo-3D wire-frame graphics; its world is viewed from a first-person perspective. It has no overarching story, though a race known as Thargoids play the role of antagonists: their ships will often attack the player-controlled ship, forcing the player to engage in space combat. Combat is action-oriented, taking place in the same environment as the exploration. The player must use various weapons the ship is equipped with, as well as manoeuvre the ship, trying to dodge enemy attacks. The player can also choose to attack neutral ships; doing so will decrease the protagonist's reputation, eventually attracting the attention of the galactic police.

Elite is notable for its expansive game world, consisting of eight galaxies and 256 planets. The player is free to travel to any of these planets, provided his ship has enough fuel for the trip (the ship's fuel capacity is limited for a journey to the distance of seven light years). </desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Elite-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Elite-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David Braben</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pirates of the Barbary Coast.zip</path>
		<name>Pirates Of The Barbary Coast</name>
		<desc>A business/strategy/RPG-like simulation.

You play as a captain named Articus whose daughter is kidnapped by Bloodthroat, a "lecherous pirate".  You must raise 50,000 gold pieces as ransom, by transporting goods and battling nefarious high-seas pirates.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Pirates of the Barbary Coast-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>StarSoft Development Laboratories</developer>
		<publisher>StarSoft Development Laboratories</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deliverance.zip</path>
		<name>Deliverance</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Deliverance-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Deliverance-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Deliverance-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>20th Century Fox</developer>
		<publisher>20th Century Fox</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lurking Horror, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Lurking Horror</name>
		<desc>(From the Infocom Home Page site)

In The Lurking Horror, you are a student at G.U.E. Tech. You have braved a snowstorm to get to the Computer Center and finish work on an assignment. But the snowstorm has turned into a raging blizzard, and has trapped you in a complex of buildings late at night. You are not alone, fortunely ... or perhaps, unfortunately. Thus you begin the story, unaware that anything may be wrong beneath or within the veneer of the quiet campus.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Lurking Horror, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Lurking Horror, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Lurking Horror, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infocom</developer>
		<publisher>Infocom</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ivanhoe.zip</path>
		<name>Ivanhoe</name>
		<desc>A scrolling beat 'em up along the lines of the Streets of Rage series. Our hero is armed with a sword. He must progress through lots of tough levels in order to save the princess. He has various ways of slashing at opponents with his sword. The game features large characters with animation indicating clumsy lumbering movement.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Ivanhoe-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ivanhoe-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ivanhoe-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ivanhoe-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ThunderWing.zip</path>
		<name>Thunderwing</name>
		<desc>The player controls Thunderwing, an ?Urban Air Fighter?, which is stolen to help the rebel forces against some suppressor.nnnnThe game is a vertical scrolling shooter. The ship is equipped with lasers and can activate the disruptor, a force field around the ship, destroying everything near. There are differently colored enemy formations, which give different rewards on complete destruction: a red formation rewards an update to the basic laser cannon, destroying two blue and two red formation is rewarded with an extra live. Some ground enemies leave a reload to the limited disruptor. There are end-of-level bosses to defeat.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/ThunderWing-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/ThunderWing-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artronics</developer>
		<publisher>Cascade Games</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Catch 23.zip</path>
		<name>Catch 23</name>
		<desc>The CK23 is a plane that can take off and land like an ordinary plane, but can fly into space and orbit the earth for weeks on end. When it's ready it can swoop back to the earth destroying all in it's path. It's Development site is on a highly guarded mountainous deserted island surrounded by minefields, electric fences and numerous vehicle and foot patrols. The major problem is that it belongs to your enemy. You have been parachuted in (where you land is down to the wind) to enter the heart of the development complex, take the blueprints to the plane and set a time delay detonator in the nuclear reactor. You have eight hours till sunrise to complete your mission.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Catch 23-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Catch 23-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Catch 23-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Communications Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Martech</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bumpy.zip</path>
		<name>Bumpy</name>
		<desc>The first game in the Bumpy series is, just like its sequels, about a head that can bump a lot. You control whether the head shall bump left or right, and how far up it will bounce, across a series of bouncy platforms. Once you have picked up all items on the screen, the exit appears so that you can go on to the next screen. 

While most platforms are perfectly harmless, some have additional qualities, such as being destructible, thereby granting access to other parts of the screen. Some platforms are on fire, which will turn out lethal unless you have picked up a water droplet in advance. 

Bumpy was remade for 16-bit platforms as Pop-Up, and then ported back once more to the Amstrad CPC.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Bumpy-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Bumpy-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bumpy-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Loriciels</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciels</publisher>
		<genre>Variados</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Face-Off Ice Hockey.zip</path>
		<name>Face Off</name>
		<desc>The action in this ice hockey game is viewed from a side-scrolling perspective with a semi-3D effect. The puck loosely sticks to the player as he skates, and the netminders are CPU-controlled. Fights and penalties can be turned on or off, and the length of the match can be varied. 

As well as individual one or two player modes, a full managerial mode is included. This sees you take control of an international team and guide them through a full schedule of matches, including developing their skills and team-work.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Face-Off Ice Hockey-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Face-Off Ice Hockey-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Face-Off Ice Hockey-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Face-Off Ice Hockey-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Krisalis Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eye of Horus.zip</path>
		<name>The Eye of Horus</name>
		<desc>As a mystical shaman, go through a pyramid in ancient Egypt to get the magical eye of horus. In a cool twist, by pressing the up arrow you turn into a birdy and can search through the levels. Just press the down arrow and voila! Human again. Many traps try to trick you.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Eye of Horus-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Eye of Horus-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Eye of Horus-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Britannica Software</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beyond the Ice Palace.zip</path>
		<name>Beyond the Ice Palace</name>
		<desc>This platform romp has similarities to Ghosts 'N Goblins, sending you on a journey to defeat the forces of evil. You start the game with nine lives, and you'll need them although there are only 3 (large) levels, each finishing with a boss. All manner of monsters block your path and must be attacked with your horizontally-travelling daggers. Additional weapons can be collected, as can bonus orbs, and the chance to summon a spirit to attack for you on the toughest sections.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Beyond the Ice Palace-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Beyond the Ice Palace-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Beyond the Ice Palace-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blues Brothers, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Blues Brothers</name>
		<desc>The Blues Brothers are on the run from the law. Take control of either bulky Jake or nippy Elwood in this five-level platform game. You must cross a prison, a river and the big city to reach freedom. You also must find your missing records and collect these. Everything and everyone is against you, but you can pick up and throw warehouse crates to defeat your opponents.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Blues Brothers, The-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Blues Brothers, The-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Blues Brothers, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Blues Brothers, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bob Winner.zip</path>
		<name>Bob Winner</name>
		<desc>Bob Winner is searching for a lost civilisation somewhere in the desert, and has to gain three keys to access it by beating a boss in Paris, London, and New York respectively. The first two bosses are boxers, the last one is a gun-toting cowboy. The items necessary to beat the bosses are found on the preceding screens.

So far the rather weak story for this typical French side-view flip-screen action adventure that focuses not so much on combat but on avoiding rather unmotivated rolling barrels and flying insects and is remarkable mainly because of its at the time outstanding graphics.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Bob Winner-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Bob Winner-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Bob Winner-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Bob Winner-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Loriciels</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciels</publisher>
		<genre>Luta</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trash Heap.zip</path>
		<name>Trash Heap</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Trash Heap-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Trash Heap-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tommy Software</developer>
		<publisher>Diamond</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wanderer 3D.zip</path>
		<name>Wanderer</name>
		<desc>Wanderer is set in the future where cats have become very valuable. The hero's cat has been kidnapped by someone who demands 8000 cats as ransom. Additionally, all the planets of the universe are obsessed with an poker-like card game. So the player visits planets, barters cards and plays the card game - and if a planet is satisfied with their own set, they reward the player with cats.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Wanderer 3D-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lankhor</developer>
		<publisher>Pyramide Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nitro Boost Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Nitro Boost Challenge</name>
		<desc>In Nitro Boost Challenge, the player takes the role of a stunt man who has to drive a car through five dangerous film scenes. This game is a vertically scrolling shooter in which the player has to dodge bombs dropped from the sky, other cars which use guns to damage the player's vehicle and stationary obstacles on the ground. The player has a gun to shoot back, but the main challenge is to finish the course within the time limit. The player can control the speed of the car and use nitro pills for a temporary boost. If too much damage is sustained, the player dies.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Nitro Boost Challenge-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Nitro Boost Challenge-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Code Masters</developer>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Timeblast.zip</path>
		<name>Timeblast</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Timeblast-image.png</image>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./I, Ball.zip</path>
		<name>I, Ball</name>
		<desc>Terry Ball (terrible, geddit?) has kidnapped Lover Ball, No Ball, Eddy Ball and Glow Ball, and I,Ball must rescue them through 16 stages. The gameplay is shoot 'em up based, with the 16 levels scrolling vertically. They are full of hazards ranging from st</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/I, Ball-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/I, Ball-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/I, Ball-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paragon Software</developer>
		<publisher>Silverbird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harley-Davidson - The Road to Sturgis.zip</path>
		<name>Harley Davidson</name>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Harley-Davidson - The Road to Sturgis-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Harley-Davidson - The Road to Sturgis-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Harley-Davidson - The Road to Sturgis-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incredible Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre></genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Real Ghostbusters, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Real Ghostbusters</name>
		<desc>Após o sucesso do filme "Caça-Fantasmas" (e do jogo homônimo,licenciado pela Actvision), uma séria animada foi criada, e um jogo de arcade baseado nela foi desenvolvido pela Data East. Neste jogo, você controla um Caça-Fantasmas, passando por 10 fases cheias de fantasmas, que você deve exterminar.

Para isso, você deve atirar nos fantasmas usando uma arma, e então usar um raio de fótons(Apertando e segurando o botão de tiro), e sugá-los para dentro do compartimento de armazenamento de sua mochila. Recargas do raio de fóton pode ser coletadas, assim como, é possível realizar melhorias em suas armas e escudos. O famoso mascote "Geléia" também aparece nesse jogo, como um poder especial, rodeando o personagem e matando os fantasmas que tocarem nele.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Real Ghostbusters, The-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Real Ghostbusters, The-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Real Ghostbusters, The-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Archipelagos.zip</path>
		<name>Archipel</name>
		<desc>Archipelagos is a real-time puzzle and strategy game with an unconventional premise and equally unconventional gameplay.

In the future, man carelessly poisons the earth with nuclear waste. The polar ice caps have melted, turning the surface of the earth into many islands of decaying land masses, known as Archipelagos. Man then built systems to try to clean up the pollution, but these failed. The only life left were genetically-altered plants made in an effort to clean up the waste -- these also turned hostile. It is up to you to clean up the earth, island by island.  

Controlling a hoversphere, it is up to you to make Earth's many islands of land habitable. To do this, you need to knock out the radiation generators on each island, which can be done by knocking out each generator's power sources (there are several per island). Once these are knocked out, you have 90 seconds to get back to the generator and disable it before it melts down, taking you with it.

Obstacles, unfortunately for you, are plentiful: You can't knock out a power source unless it is connected by a "land bridge" to the generator. You have the ability to create land where needed, but this takes up energy, and you have a limited supply. Also a hindrance are the many genetically-altered entities left behind on the islands: Viral trees that poison the ground; necromancers (former hoverspheres) that now erode land instead of creating it; eco eggs that explode on touch; and aircleaners, who are ruthlessly efficient in cleaning up the air -- and everything else, including you.

The entire game plays from a 3D first-person viewpoint. A movable cursor selects where to move or what to manipulate.

There are 10,000 islands on Earth to purify. If you can make it past Archipelago #100, you are then free to select any of them.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Archipelagos-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Archipelagos-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Archipelagos-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Astral Software</developer>
		<publisher>Logotron Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jewels of Darkness.zip</path>
		<name>Jewels Of Darkness</name>
		<desc>This is a collection of three previously-published Rainbird interactive fiction (with graphics) games. It contains:

1. Adventure Quest
2. Colossal Adventure
2. Dungeon Adventure</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Jewels of Darkness-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Jewels of Darkness-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Jewels of Darkness-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Level 9 Computing</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Business.zip</path>
		<name>Monster Business</name>
		<desc>Monster Business is influenced by vintage platformers such as Mr. Do and Dig Dug. Bob owns a zoo, but the creatures (monkeys, snakes and all the rest) have gone on the rampage and must be stopped.
Its levels contain ledges, ramps, and similar, and scroll vertically. Bob must aim his short range gun at them for long enough to cause them to explode, then release to send them up the screen, and ideally hit them again, to release as many bonus fruits as possible. This must all be done within a time limit – complete it before being told to hurry up and you get a time bonus.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Monster Business-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Monster Business-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Monster Business-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eclipse Software Design</developer>
		<publisher>Ascon GmbH</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Truck Racing.zip</path>
		<name>International Truck Racing</name>
		<desc>This overhead view racing game is a serious simulation of the exciting sport of truck racing. This explains the apparently slow, jerky scrolling and rickety collisions, as this is how real trucks handle.

There are 6 trucks in each race, which take place across famed international circuits. Every couple of laps you must refuel, which is done by driving into the pits and collecting the flag in your car’s colour. The top 3 finishers in each race score points, and you must finish in the top 3 to progress to the next round.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/International Truck Racing-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/International Truck Racing-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/International Truck Racing-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zeppelin Games Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Zeppelin Games Limited</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mafdet and the Book of the Dead.zip</path>
		<name>Mafdet and the Book of the Dead</name>
		<desc>The story starts in ancient Egypt. The evil god, Seth, has stolen The Book of the Dead and hidden it deep in the underworld. Without The Book, no egyptian man or woman will be able to enter the afterlife when they die - their soul will be condemned to walk the earth until the spells in the book are read.
You are Mafdet, the cat Goddess of Revenge, who has been summoned by Isis (the Goddess of Earth) to retrieve the book and return it to the Egyptian people.
You will need to use all your strength and intelligence to find the book, which is well guarded by Seth's minions. Collect amulets which will help you along your way; change between cat and human to help you pass some obstacles; find your way through mazed and dungeons; above all - FIND THE BOOK. All Egypt has put its trust in you.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Mafdet and the Book of the Dead-image.png</image>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mafdet and the Book of the Dead-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradox</developer>
		<publisher>Software Horizons</publisher>
		<genre>Briga de rua</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Continental Circus.zip</path>
		<name>Continental Circus</name>
		<desc>The home conversions of Continental Circus lack the full-on 3D and special glasses of the arcade version, but retain the essential gameplay structure. The first race is in Brazil and features 100 cars, and requires you to finish in the top 80 in order to qualify for  next race. As you work through the 8 races the size of the field steadily decreases, but so does the worst acceptable finishing position to qualify.

The car has high and low gears, and is susceptible to damage from contact with another car. Once you hit a car or a piece of the trackside scenery you will be called into the pits - fail to make it back, or hit another car, and you will crash and lose several seconds.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Continental Circus-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Continental Circus-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Continental Circus-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Continental Circus-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spitting Image.zip</path>
		<name>Spitting Image</name>
		<desc>This game is based on the long-running British satirical television show with puppet likenesses of political figures and celebrities. A prophet determines that a world war will occur in seven years instigated by a mysterious leader. To avoid this, one ruler of the world must be determined in this beat 'em up involving six rulers: U.S.A.'s Ronald Regan, the U.K.'s Margaret Thatcher, the USSR's Mikhail Gorbachev, South Africa's PW Botha, Iran's Ayathollah Khomeini, and Pope John Paul II.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Spitting Image-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Spitting Image-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Spitting Image-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Walking Circles</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Never Mind.zip</path>
		<name>Never Mind</name>
		<desc>Sua tarefa é reconstruir uma série de fotos coletando peças dispersas e coloca-las na sequência correta. É uma tarefa aparentemente simples, mas não se deixe enganar. Você também terá que lidar com peças de xadrez comprimindo peças, peças dissolvíveis e pontes, peças transportadoras e um tempo limite terrivelmente apertado.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Never Mind-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Never Mind-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Never Mind-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>M.C. Lothlorien</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Get Dexter.zip</path>
		<name>Get Dexter</name>
		<desc>Crafton the android wants a life of freedom, away from the science experiments he is usually subjected to. Escaping the compound will require a security code, which is split into eight parts. Find the scientists who hold these to escape, in this isometric arcade adventure.

There are obstacles to interact with, and foes to work around. Contact with these drains your energy, but there are Nurse pods to recharge this. There are four types of barrier doors - red, green, blue and grey, each requiring their own keys. You are accompanied by Xunk, who can be used to help with this - he will also warn you of events as they unfold, and automatically follow you to the exit of each screen.</desc>
		<image>./media/screenhots/Get Dexter-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/Get Dexter-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Get Dexter-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ere Informatique</developer>
		<publisher>Ere Informatique</publisher>
		<genre>Aventura</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
